你真是不可思议。
You were incredible.
我的心还在狂跳。
My heart is still racing.
我也感觉到了。
I felt it too.
这都要归功于你的蛮力，Dash。
All thanks to your brute strength, Dash,
以及你对古代阿拉姆语数学的了解。
and your knowledge of ancient Aramaic mathematics.
请注意。这与我的两个博士学位没有关系
Please. This has nothing to do with my two doctorates
和我的性别研究硕士课程
and my master's in Gender Studies
和所有与你有关的事情，洛夫莫尔博士。
and everything to do with you, Dr. Lovemore.
事实是。
The truth is,
我从未想过我能找到失落的D城。
I never thought I would find the Lost City of D.
我会仔细选择你的措辞。
I would choose your words carefully.
他们将是你的最后一次。
They will be your last.
你带我到卡拉曼国王的墓前
You led me right to King Kalaman's tomb
和他的女王的传奇性的火之冠。
and his queen's legendary Crown of Fire.
现在我将变得非常富有。
And now I will be very rich,
而你将会死得很惨。
and you will be very dead.
暂停。这些是...这些是你的蛇吗？
Hold up. Are these... Are these your snakes?
不，他们只是在这里。
No, they were just here.
这座寺庙里有数百条蛇
There were just hundreds of snakes in this temple
只是在等待我们出现？
just waiting for us to show up?
- 谁喂养它们？你喂他们？
- 不，他们吃什么？
- Who feeds them? You feed them?
- No, what do they eat?
为什么那个人没有咬那个人？为什么会出现这种情况？
Why is that one not biting that guy? Why is that happening?
- 他们是否接受过不咬随从或其他方面的训练？
- 是的，嗯...
- Are they trained not to bite henchmen or something?
- Yeah, well...
我的意思是，光是蛇与寺庙的比例...
I mean, the snake-to-temple ratio alone...
这很荒唐。删除。
This is ridiculous. Delete.
I...我想我的性格还是可以的。
I... I think my character can still work.
删除。
Delete.
洛雷塔，你仍然有一个故事要写。
Loretta, you still have a story to write.
删除。
Delete.
嘿，是我，贝丝。。
Hey, it's me, Beth.
我不想打出 "我是你的出版商 "的牌，但我就是这样。
I don't want to pull the whole "I'm your publisher" card, but I am.
而且我真的很期待看到这最后一章。
And I'm really looking forward to seeing this last chapter.
但没有压力。不，实际上有压力。
But no pressure. No, there actually is pressure.
确切的压力量可以激励你，但不会使你瘫痪。。
The exact amount of pressure that motivates you but doesn't paralyze you.
你得到这个。
You got this.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
又是我。
Me again.
好的，所以一切都准备好了，以便进行图书巡回展，。
Okay, so everything is set for the book tour,
但是，呃，我们唯一需要的是一本可以巡回展出的书。
but, uh, the only thing we need is a book to tour with.
我不禁有一种感觉，你没有完成。
I can't help but get the feeling that you're not finishing
因为你不想离开你的房子。。
because you don't want to leave your house.
听着，我知道在约翰去世后的这五年很艰难，。
Listen, I know these last five years have been hard after John's passing,
在你的浴缸里生活感觉更轻松，。
and it feels easier to live in your bathtub,
在冰上喝霞多丽。
drinking Chardonnay on ice.
但是，女孩，有一个很大的世界在等着你。
But, girl, there is a great big world waiting for you
还有一个我不能取消的巡回售书活动，所以请务必实现它，好吗？
and a book tour that I can't cancel, so just make it happen, all right?
爱你，再见！。
Love you, bye!
我们必须继续前进。。
We have to keep going.
让我们看看那扇门的另一边有什么。
Let's see what's on the other side of that door.
但如果什么都没有呢？
But what if there isn't anything?
只有一个办法可以找到答案。
There's only one way to find out.
然后Lovemore意识到
Then Lovemore realized
她想要的宝藏永远失去了
the treasure she wanted was lost forever
而她的冒险也即将结束。
and her adventures were coming to an end.
这感觉不对。
That doesn't feel right.
是的，但仅此而已。
Yeah, but that's it.
这就结束了。
That's the end.
好吧，约翰。
Well, John,
在这里，我走了。
here I go.
Dulcius ex asperis.。
Dulcius ex asperis.
- 好了，亲爱的，表演时间到了。
- 你确定这一点吗？
- Okay, honey, it's showtime.
- Are you sure about this?
因为我在这个东西里，后面和前面都有一个楔子。
Because I have a wedgie in the back and in the front in this thing.
我觉得自己像一个呆板的花样滑冰运动员。
I feel like a nerdy figure skater.
- 性感。Stunner。我都是这样的。
- 不，不是的。它不是。
- Sexy. Stunner. I'm all about it.
- No, it's not. It's not.
- 我如何在这里面移动？
- 不要碰它。
- How do I move in this?
- Don't touch it.
- 我没有碰它。我把它拿出来了。
- 停止吧。你会停下来吗？
- I'm not touching it. I'm holding it out.
- Stop it. Will you stop?
现在就把它拿出来，因为你不能在舞台上这样做。
Get it out now 'cause you can't do that onstage.
我们已经完成了。我们已经完成了。好的，很好。
And we're done. And we're done. Okay, good.
我需要穿上闪闪发光的连衣裙吗？
Do I need to be wearing a glitter onesie?
你只需要穿两个小时就可以了。
You only have to wear this for two hours.
不要搞砸了，你听到了吗？这是借来的。
Do not mess this up, do you hear me? This is on loan.
现在每个人都在穿亮片。
Everyone's wearing sequins right now.
- 她为什么要拍我的照片？
- 这就是艾莉森。
- Why is she taking my photo?
- This is Allison.
她是我们新的社会媒体经理。
She is our new social media manager.
她将帮助我们瞄准年轻群体。
And she's gonna be helping us target that younger demographic.
意思是30多岁的女性，希望她们在20多岁的时候。
Meaning women in their 30s who wish they were in their 20s.
嘿，怎么了？
Hey, what's up?
嗯，我接管了你的社交网站，所以今天早上你发了推特。
Um, I took over your socials, so this morning you tweeted,
"我的女士们在哪里？下午5点在G宴会厅等我。
"Where are my ladies at? Meet me at Ballroom G at 5:00 p.m.
#ShawnMendes。
#ShawnMendes.
#GaggingToMeetYouAll"。
#GaggingToMeetYouAll."
好了，我们正在享受乐趣。我们走吧。
Okay, we are having fun. Let's go.
我们需要提醒人们，你还活着。
We need to remind people that you are still alive.
人们知道我还活着。
People know I'm alive.
并提醒他们为什么这曾经是
And to remind them why this used to be
- 最畅销的特许经营权。
- 在浪漫中。
- the best selling franchise.
- In Romance.
是的，这是创收最多的文学类别。
Yes, which is the top revenue-generating literary category.
创收并不是我现在要描述我们的预售。
Revenue-generating isn't how I would describe our presales right now.
就把这看作是一种利用口碑的方式。
Just think of this as a way that uses word of mouth.
哦，你想要口碑？在这里，我们走了。这个怎么样？
Oh, you want word of mouth? Here we go. How's this?
"唯一比城市更迷失的是作者本人"。
"The only thing more lost than the city is the author herself."
"无爱"。
"没有激情"。
"Loveless."
"Passionless."
呃，"已经过了她的黄金时期"。还有，哦。
"这是最糟糕的假历史"。
Uh, "Way past her prime." And, oh,
"This is fake history at its worst."
一次图书巡展可以改变一切，好吗？
A book tour could change everything, okay?
我们必须提醒粉丝们为什么他们这么爱你。
We have to remind the fans why they love you so much.
真实的历史。我只是把它换成了多一点的裸体。
Real history. I merely season it with a smidge more nudity.
历史上有大量的裸体行为。
History had a ton of nudity.
深入探索。
Deep exploration.
Steamy想知道。
Steamy wondering.
Lovemore和Dash能否找到塔哈女王无价的火之冠？。
Will Lovemore and Dash find Queen Taha's priceless Crown of Fire?
加入他们的搜索。。
Join them on their search.
所以，听着，我想和你谈谈一些事情。
So, listen, I wanted to talk to you about something.
有这么多的人。
There's so many people.
我知道你有多讨厌做这些事情。
I know how much you hate doing these things,
所以我今天邀请了艾伦来和大家做问答。
so I've invited Alan to do the Q and A with you today.
- 什么？
- 还有其余的图书之旅。
- What?
- And the rest of the book tour.
贝丝，我明确要求不要再和小飞做任何活动了......阿兰，阿兰!
Beth, I expressly asked not to do any more events with Dash... Alan, Alan!
- 他要羞辱我。
- 他不会羞辱你。
- He's gonna humiliate me.
- He's not gonna humiliate you.
谢谢你。你的工作非常出色。非常感谢你。谢谢你。
Thank you. You're very good at your job. Thank you so much. Thank you.
让我来帮助你。
Let me help you with that.
他是...他是一个沐浴露广告。
He is... He's a body wash commercial.
他总是浑身闪闪发光。
He's always glistening all over the place.
没有一次活动他的衬衫没有飞起来。
There hasn't been an event where his shirt didn't come flying off.
- 你希望如此。
- 嗯，他已经在这里了。
- You wish.
- Well, he's already here,
因此，穿上你的大女孩内裤，让我们去那里。
so put on your big-girl panties and let's get out there.
请记住，不要有暴躁的脸，大话或无聊的学术谈话。
Remember, no grumpy face, big words or boring academic talk.
是的，是的。
Yes! Yes!
来吧，RTP!
Come on, RTP!
哈-哈!
Ha-ha!
是的，我的Lovemore-heads!
Yes, my Lovemore-heads!
我很高兴向你介绍
I am so excited to introduce to you
获奖作家洛雷塔-塞奇!
the award-winning author, Loretta Sage!
- 贝丝，我不能这样做。我还没准备好。
- 你在跟我开玩笑吗？
- Beth, I can't do this. I'm not ready.
- Are you kidding me?
听着，我支持你。你有这个。
Listen, I've got your back. You got this.
去给人民他们想要的东西。
Go give the people what they want.
- 他们要的不是我。
- 现在就出去吧!
- It's not me they want.
- Get out there now!
嗨，你好吗？很高兴见到你。谢谢你。
Hi. How are you? Nice to see you. Thank you.
是的。装上它。
Yep. Mount it.
装上它。装上它。好的。
Mount it. Mount it. Okay.
找到你的中心。
Find your center.
而现在，你们都在等待的时刻。
And now, the moment you've all been waiting for.
- 最性感的...
- 好的！
- The sexiest...
- All right!
...一代人中最有影响力的英雄。
...most influential hero of a generation.
这话说得有点重。
That's a bit strong.
他的第20本安吉拉-洛夫莫尔小说的封面。
His 20th cover of an Angela Lovemore novel.
Dash McMahon!
哦，我的上帝！小飞！
Oh, my God! Dash!
- 鞠躬吧。
- 我已经做了我的。我做了我的。
- Take a bow.
- I already did mine. I did mine.
好吧，来吧。再来一个。我抓住你了。
Okay, come on. One more. I got you.
你们排练过吗？哦，我的天。
Did you guys rehearse that? Oh, my God.
我很喜欢你们俩之间的这种化学反应，我得说。
I'm loving this chemistry between you two, and I got to say,
我喜欢这本书。
I love this book.
- 哦，谢谢你，雷。
- 谢谢...
- Oh, thank you, Ray.
- Thank...
扰流板警告。
Spoiler alert.
一个非常大胆的选择
A really bold choice
为了不让他们在最后进入坟墓。
to not have them go into the tomb at the end.
谈谈这一次是怎么做的。
Talk about what went into this one.
我的意思是，这本书对我个人来说是如此特别。
I mean, this one's such a special book for me personally.
I...我不知道该怎么说它对我的意义有多大
I... I don't know how to say how much it means to me
那位洛雷塔，文字作家的特长。
that Loretta, word writer extraordinaire,
已经，你知道，以我的名字命名这本书。
has, you know, named the book after me.
《失落的达什之城》。
The Lost City of Dash.
《失落的D城》。
The Lost City of D.
嗯，但这不是D所代表的含义。
Um, but that's not what the D stands for.
- 是 "D "的意思，对吗？
- 没有鸡巴，没有。
- It's D for "dick," right?
- No dick, no.
它是基于一个古老部落的名字，Dapocagihou-dysphem-ica。
It's based on the name of an ancient tribe, Dapocagihou-dysphem-ica.
而且，嗯，这对欧洲殖民者来说太难发音了。
And, um, it was too difficult for the European colonizers to pronounce,
- 因此，以真正的殖民主义方式，他们把它缩写了。
- 没有人关心这个问题。
- so, in true colonial fashion they abbreviated it.
- No one cares about this.
这真是太有趣了。好的。
That's so interesting. Okay.
我们从观众那里接受一些问题如何？
How about we take some questions from the audience?
- 就在这里，帅哥！
- 是的。
- Right here, handsome!
- Yes.
- 小飞，你最喜欢的浪漫时刻是什么？
- 哦。
- Dash, what's your favorite romantic moment?
- Ooh.
我真正想知道的是，洛雷塔最喜欢的浪漫时刻是什么？
What I would really like to know is what is Loretta's favorite romantic moment?
哦，辣的。
Ooh, spicy.
哦，呃...
Oh, uh...
好吧，作为一个无性恋者...
Well, being a sapiosexual...
哦，是当他们做的蛇周围的...
Oh, is that when they do the snakes around the...
不，那是一个发现，呃，智力的人
No. That's someone who finds, uh, intellect
或智慧，呃，非常性感，你知道。
or intelligence, uh, very sexy, you know.
一样。
Same.
真的吗？
Really?
冲啊！扯掉你的衬衫！
Dash! Rip off your shirt!
不，不，不。我们今天不打算这么做。我们是为洛雷塔的书而来。
No, no, no. We're not gonna do that today. We're here for Loretta's book.
我们有问题要问Loretta吗？
Do we have questions for Loretta?
呃，是的，看起来很好学的年轻女士？你想问我什么？
Uh, yes, studious-looking young lady? What would you like to ask me?
你能撕掉小飞的衬衫吗？
Can you rip off Dash's shirt?
不，不。我们不会再这样做了。对不起。
No, no. We're not gonna do this again. Sorry.
撕掉它!撕掉它！
Rip it off! Rip it off!
撕掉它!撕掉它！扯掉它！ 扯掉它！
Rip it off! Rip it off! Rip it off!
当然了。当然，是的。可以做。
Of course. Of course, yes. Can do.
有这种情况吗？
Is this happening?
- 你不需要这样做。
- 哦，我们必须这样做。
- You don't have to do this.
- Oh, we have to.
我们必须给人民他们想要的东西。是的，是的。
We have to give the people what they want. Yes, yes.
我们必须给人民他们想要的东西，是的。
We have to give the people what they want, yes.
女士们，先生们，请欣赏。
Ladies and gentlemen, enjoy.
因为《失落的D城》。
是小飞的最后一次冒险。
Because The Lost City of D
is Dash's final adventure.
如果甚至有下一本书的话。
If there even is a next book,
它将以Lovemore收到悲惨的消息开始
it will open with Lovemore receiving the tragic news
他英年早逝的消息。
of his untimely death.
什么？
What?
- 该死的。我很抱歉。我的智能手表被卡住了。
- 嗷。坚持住。
- Shit. I'm sorry. My smartwatch is stuck.
- Ow. Hold on.
我知道。不要拉它。
I know. Don't pull it.
没关系的。只要仍然是真实的。
It's okay. Just be real still.
- 不，那是在拉动它。
- 你在拉动它。
- No. That's pulling it.
- You're pulling it.
你要把我的假发扯下来。不，你不能...
You're gonna rip my wig off. No, you can't...
哦，我的天啊!
Oh, my!
- 哦，我的上帝。
- 他还好吗？
- Oh, my God.
- Is he okay?
上帝，我很抱歉。我真的很抱歉。
God, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- 我很抱歉。
- 你是个坏人。
- I'm so sorry.
- You're a bad person.
晚上6点，坚持参加服装比赛。
Stick around for the costume contest at 6:00 p.m.
"如果有另一本书"？
"If there is another book"?
我将把我们的一切都投入到这次巡演中，好吗？
I'm investing everything we've got into this tour, okay?
我只是不认为我有另一个Dash和Lovemore的冒险。
I just don't think I have another Dash and Lovemore adventure in me.
小飞是怎么死的？
How does Dash die?
- 是蛇的问题吗？
- 没有。
- Was it the snakes?
- No.
好的，所以我有一些事情必须要处理。
Okay, so I have something that I have to take care of.
10分钟后，你们在隔壁套房有一个采访。
You guys have an interview in the next suite in ten minutes.
所以，你们能不能帮我一个忙，做个大人？
So can you please do me a favor and be grown-ups
并让你们自己去那里？
and get yourselves there on your own?
好的。非常感谢你。
Okay. Thank you so much.
他是否死于葡萄球菌感染？
Does he die from a staph infection?
它是一种葡萄球菌感染。我知道它。
It is a staph infection. I knew it.
我...好的。
I-I... All right.
听着，如果你需要休息或什么，我明白。
Look, I get it if you need a break or something,
- 但你不能就这样杀了我，好吗？
- 好的。
- but you can't just kill me, okay?
- Okay.
我讨厌我必须这样问，但你知道你不是大飞，对吗？
I hate that I have to ask this, but you do know you're not Dash, right?
小飞是我编造的一个角色。
Dash is a character I made up.
潇洒？
Dash?
谢谢。
Thanks.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
- 洛雷塔，是这样的。
- 不，我认为是这样的。
- Loretta, it's this way.
- No, I think it's this way.
难道你看不出小飞对人们意味着什么吗？
Can't you see that Dash means so much to people?
- 对你来说意义重大。
- 对我来说不是。
- Means so much to you.
- Not to me.
嗯，是的，对我来说，但对其他人来说也是如此。
Well, yeah, to me, but to other people too.
- 贝丝怎么样了？
- 你知道吗？贝丝会好起来的。
- What about Beth?
- You know what? Beth is gonna be fine.
她会发现很多新鲜的、充满伟大思想的年轻作家。
She's gonna find plenty fresh, young writers full of great ideas.
你可以优雅地过渡
You can transition gracefully
进入你的模特生涯的穿衣阶段。
into the shirt-on phase of your modeling career,
而我可以独处。
and I can be left alone.
大家都很高兴。
Everybody is happy.
不，是这样的。
No, it's this way.
贝丝说你甚至不再离开房子了。
Beth says you don't even leave the house anymore.
我觉得这不是很开心。
I don't feel like that's very happy.
你应该到外面的世界去，用新的经验来充实自己。
You should be going out in the world, filling yourself up on new experiences.
我已经被填满了。我已经饱了。我已经完全吃饱了。
I'm already filled up. I'm full. I'm fully satiated.
当你可以看到这个世界时，你为什么想一个人呆在家里呢？
Why would you want to be stuck at home alone when you could see the world?
你可能是在访问古希腊。
You could be visiting ancient Greece.
好吧，我怎么能访问古希腊呢？
Okay. How could I visit ancient Greece?
我明白了。因为你害怕飞行。
I get it. Because you're afraid of flying.
不，因为古希腊已经成为过去。
No. Because ancient Greece is in the past.
就像Dash一样。
Just like Dash.
好吧，你想知道还有谁停留在过去吗？你是。
Okay. You want to know who else is stuck in the past? You are.
你如此害怕生活再次伤害你，以至于你已经停止生活。
You're so afraid of life hurting you again that you've stopped living.
你就像一个人类的木乃伊。
You're like a human mummy.
我没有，嗯...
I didn't, um...
哦。
Oh.
木乃伊是人类。
Mummies are human.
愚蠢的...哦，糟糕。
Stupid... Oh, crap.
我很抱歉。我......我会把它清理干净的。
I'm so sorry. I-I will clean this up.
我不是一个爱乱丢东西的人，我向你保证。
I am not a litterer, I-I assure you that.
你，嗯...你认为你可以，呃，为我叫一辆车，好吗？
Do you, um... Do you think you could, uh, call a car for me, please?
谢谢你。谢谢你。
Thank you. Thank you.
把车开过来。
Bring the car around.
天啊，那是某人的聘金吗？
God, is that someone's retainer?
我在她身边从来没有说过一次正确的话。
I've never said the right thing one time around her.
我感到紧张，因为她开口了。
I get nervous because she opens her mouth,
和只是一个美丽的百科全书出来，和我只是从来没有说...
and just an encyclopedia of beautifulness comes out, and I just never say...
你知道她想杀我吗？
You know she's trying to kill me?
我只是需要那些西红柿。
I just need those tomatoes.
你是对的。不，你是对的。
You're right. No, you're right.
我应该道歉。谢谢你，伙计。
I should apologize. Thank you, man.
- 我非常、非常欣赏这一点。
- 不客气。
- I appreciate that very, very much.
- You're welcome.
呃，洛雷塔-塞奇。是的。
Uh, Loretta Sage. Yeah.
呃...
Uh...
你好。
Hiya.
呃，我没有订购UberPool。
Uh, I did not order an UberPool.
有人要见你。我们会让你马上回来。
Someone wants to meet you. We'll have you right back.
嗯...
Um...
洛雷塔!
Loretta!
洛雷塔！洛雷塔？洛雷塔？
Loretta! Loretta?
呃，洛雷塔？
Uh, Loretta?
- 你说 "洛雷塔 "吗？
- 是的。
- Did you say "Loretta"?
- Yeah.
- 跟着那辆SUV，伙计。
- 没有。
- Follow that SUV, man.
- No.
- 来吧，请！
- 不，不，不。
- Come on, please!
- No, no, no.
我不会再帮助任何英俊的陌生人了。骗我一次吧。嗯，嗯，嗯。
I'm not helping any more handsome strangers. Fool me once. Mm-mmm.
这是什么，Taken？我是 "Taken "吗？
What is this, Taken? Am I "tooken"?
我已经被卖了吗？
Am I sold already?
我是不是...我被卖给他了吗？
Am I... Am I sold to him?
- 嗷。停止。
- 哦，不。这是不是感觉很惊悚？
- Ow. Stop.
- Oh, no. Did this feel creepy?
我说不要让它变得令人毛骨悚然，伙计们。
I said don't make it creepy, guys.
我对这个设置感到非常抱歉。
I'm so sorry about the setting.
我刚刚飞来。我当时真的很慌张地要见你。
I just flew in. I was in a real panic to meet you.
我没有时间把这个地方打扮得很好。
I didn't have time to dress the place up much.
我读到你喜欢奶酪，所以我就把它们都买了。
I read you love cheese, so I just got them all.
你就是那个一直给我发电子邮件要我的脚的照片的人吗？
Are you the one who's been emailing me for photos of my feet?
不，嗯...
No. Um...
我保证我将要给你看的东西会让你非常高兴。
And I promise what I'm about to show you is gonna make you very happy.
但首先，有一点
But first, a little bit
关于你面前的这个神秘的流氓。
about the mysterious rogue you see before you.
呃，我的名字是阿比盖尔-费尔法克斯。
Uh, my name is Abigail Fairfax.
- 阿比盖尔？
- 这是一个不分性别的名字，像Leslie或Beverly。
- Abigail?
- It's a gender-neutral name, like Leslie or Beverly.
是的，但你是媒体大亨费尔法克斯家族的阿比盖尔-费尔法克斯？
Yes, but you're Abigail Fairfax of the media-mogul Fairfaxes?
你不是刚刚接管了你的公司吗，还是...
Didn't you just take over your company or...
不，实际上那是我哥哥。那是莱斯利。我们都很自豪。
No, that was my brother, actually. That was Leslie. We're all very proud.
啊。是的，我应该这么说，在这样一个年轻的年龄到...
Ah. Yes, I should say so, at such a young age to...
有些人甚至会说太年轻了。
Some might even say too young.
但那个世界从未让我真正感兴趣。
But that world never really interested me.
我的激情，你可能知道。
My passions, as you may know,
躺在世界的隐秘事物中。
lie in the hidden things in the world,
不敢拥有的东西。
things which defy possession.
嗯，有人可能会说我是个收藏家。
Um, some might call me a collector.
但有一个人特别痴迷于此
But there is one obsession in particular
俘虏了我。
that has held me captive.
火之冠
The Crown of Fire
和其层层叠叠的红色钻石。
and its cascading red diamonds.
这是不是...这是一个隐藏的摄像机的事情吗？
Is this a... Is this a hidden-camera thing?
因此，想象一下我的惊讶吧，在你的新书中。
So imagine my surprise when, in your new book,
在交媾遐想的书页中。
amidst the pages of coital reverie,
是什么...
was something...
- 哦，上帝。
- ...相当宏伟。
- Oh, God.
- ...quite magnificent.
我明白了。我明白了。我现在非常明白。
I get it. I get it. I so get it right now.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, my gosh.
我真的以为是你们绑架了我。
I literally thought you guys kidnapped me.
我的意思是，这是市场营销，对吗？贝丝设置了这个？
I mean, this is marketing, right? Beth set this up?
这真是太好了，你们这些家伙。这真是太神奇了。
This was so good, you guys. This was amazing.
你，带着你的枪和你的胡子
You, with your gun and your mustache
和你的，"你最好到那里去"，你知道...
and your, "You'd better get in there" and you know...
哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你，穿着G.I.Joe色调的衣服。
You, with the G.I. Joe tone-on-tone outfit.
你虚构的考古学家正在对一种死的语言进行真实的翻译。
Your fictional archaeologist was making real translations of a dead language.
- 嗯，嗯。
- 没有其他人能够做到的事情。
- Mm-hmm.
- Something nobody else has been able to do.
好吧，没有人曾经尝试过。
Well, nobody else had ever tried.
这样做对吗？我说的对吗？
Is that right? Am I saying the right thing?
除了你，对吗？
Except you, right?
除了我!
Except me!
是的，你看，事实证明
Yes. See, it turns out
Loretta Sage曾经是一个年轻的女大学生，正在做她的论文
Loretta Sage was once a young college girl doing her dissertation
在与她未来的丈夫的D的死语言上。
on the dead language of the D with her future husband,
梦想着找到卡拉曼的坟墓和火之冠。
dreaming of finding Kalaman's tomb and the Crown of Fire.
我很遗憾地看到你在他死后放弃了你的搜索。
I was sorry to read you gave up your search after he died.
但这意味着什么呢？
But what that means is,
你是我的全部。
you're all I have left.
所有--你所剩下的......什么？
All-All you have left for... what?
嗯。
Hmm.
哦。
Oh.
在这里，我们走了。
Here we go.
这是什么？
What is this?
我相信它描述的是卡拉曼墓的确切位置。
I believe it is describing the exact location of Kalaman's tomb,
塔哈和她无价的头饰被埋在其中。
in which Taha and her priceless headdress are buried.
嗯，如果这是真实的。
Well, if this were authentic,
你还是要揭开整个城市的面纱
you would still have to uncover an entire city
没有人能够找到。
that nobody has been able to find.
我发现了它。
I found it.
在大西洋中一个被遗忘的小岛上，名为 "Hundida岛"。
On a tiny, forgotten island in the Atlantic called Isla Hundida.
我没能找到的是卡拉曼的最终安息地。
What I have not been able to find is Kalaman's final resting place.
这张羊皮纸是我们在废墟中发现的唯一线索。
This piece of parchment is the only clue we found among the ruins.
我需要一个能破译这些符号的人。
I need someone who can decipher these symbols.
我需要你。
I need you.
- 嗯...
- 赛奇小姐。
- Well...
- Miss Sage,
这肯定不是你想让你的故事结束的方式。
surely this isn't how you want your story to end.
我们都被厄运击碎了梦想。
We both had our dreams crushed by bad luck,
或者就我而言，一个拍马屁的小兄弟。
or in my case, an arse-kissing little brother,
但这是我们向他们展示所有的机会。
but this is our chance to show them all.
和我一起......到岛上来。
Come with me... to the island.
翻译这些符号，帮我找到火之冠。
Translate these symbols and help me find the Crown of Fire.
你可以说出你的价格。
You can name your price.
我必须恭敬地拒绝。
I must respectfully decline.
嗯...
Well...
我不能说我不感到失望。
I can't say I'm not disappointed.
但我理解你的感受。
But I understand how you feel.
你至少能让我们送你一程吗？
Will you at least let us give you a ride?
哦，不，谢谢你。我叫我自己的车，然后我就...
Oh, no, thank you. I'll call for my own car, and I'll just...
我不觉得你在听我说话。这很紧急，而且我们...
I don't feel like you're listening to me. This is urgent, and we...
好吧，警察说他们发出了全境通告......。
Okay, so the police are saying that they put out an APB...
- APB。
- ...在一辆SUV上。
- APB.
- ...on an SUV,
- 而且还有这个24小时的规则...
- 为什么会有这样的规定？
- and there's this 24-hour rule...
- Why is there a rule?
- ...而且他们不会做任何事情，直到...
- 那么联邦调查局或中央情报局呢？
- ...and they won't do anything until...
- What about the FBI or the CIA?
- 他们说要打电话给警察。
- 我确信洛雷塔很好。
- They said to call the police.
- I'm sure Loretta's fine.
当我在大学时，我的朋友尼基失踪了。
When I was in college, my friend Nicki went missing.
每个人都像是被吓坏了。
Everyone was, like, freaking out.
但那时她只是在她的车里。
But then she was just in her car.
她已经死了，但我们找到了她。她并没有走。
She was dead, but we found her. She wasn't gone.
嗯，那什么...也许我们可以找一个PI
Um, what about... Maybe we could get a PI
或者，像，你知道，私人保安或...
or, like, you know, private security or...
像电影中那样的救援队怎么样？
What about an extraction team, like the movie?
是的！但谁会这样做呢？退役军人，对吗？
Yes! But who does that? The ex-military, right?
哦，是的。我想我实际上有一个人可以帮助我们。
Oh, yeah. I think I actually have somebody that could help us.
- 哦。
- 我做了这个冥想闭关。
- Oh.
- I did this meditation retreat,
那里有一个培训师。
and there was this trainer guy there.
你应该看看这家伙的冥想。
You should see this guy meditate.
但他是前海豹队员。
But he's ex-Navy SEAL.
他...他是一个特别行动训练员。他叫什么名字？
He... He's a special ops trainer. What was his name?
是的。杰克-训练师。
Yeah. Jack Trainer.
所以他是一个叫杰克-训练师的训练师？
So he's a trainer named Jack Trainer?
这就是我的手机里的所有人。看，"珍妮丝妈妈"。
That's how I have everybody in my phone. See, "Janice Mom."
"拉里-门把手"。
"斯泰西屁股的东西"。
"Larry Doorknob."
"Stacy Butt Stuff."
看，这就是这家伙的工作。他找到了人。
Look, this is what this guy does. He finds people.
如果有任何人能帮助我们，那就是他。
If there's anybody that can help us, it's him.
- Jack Trainer.
- 哦，所以他的名字实际上是杰克-特拉尔。
- Oh, so his name is actually Jack Trainer.
嗨，呃，我是 "触摸你的内在 "的艾伦。
Hi, uh, this is Alan from "Touching Your Inner Self."
冥想闭关？
The meditation retreat?
总之，呃，好吧。我们的朋友Loretta被绑架了。
Anyway, uh, okay. Our friend Loretta has been kidnapped,
而没有人帮助我们。
and no one's helping us.
她失踪多久了？
How long she been missing?
也许是两个小时了。
Maybe two hours now.
那是谁？。
Who is that?
嗯，这是B...这是贝丝。我是贝丝。
Um, this is B... This is Beth. I'm Beth.
艾莉森也上场了，先生。
And Allison is on too, sir.
她有任何支持Wi-Fi的设备吗？。
Did she have any Wi-Fi-enabled devices?
- 她有她的电话，对吗？
- 不，我有她的电话。
- She's got her phone, right?
- No, I have her phone.
哦！她有一个智能手表。它把我的假发扯下来了。
Oh! She has a smartwatch. It ripped my wig off.
那是什么情景？不要紧。打开电话。
What was that scenario? Never mind. Open the phone.
- 进入智能手表应用程序。。
- 好的。
- Go to the smartwatch app.
- All right.
然后点击 "查找我的智能手表"。
Then hit "Find My Smartwatch."
哦，我的...这真是太好了。这就是我们打电话的原因。
Oh, my... That is so good. That's why we called.
"通过管理容易的事情来预测困难"。
"Anticipate the difficult by managing the easy."
- 那是奥普拉还是迪帕克？
- 老子来自《道德经》。
- Is that Oprah or Deepak?
- Laozi from Tao-te Ching.
哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
这是在大西洋。
It's in the Atlantic.
- 她在飞机上？
- 你怎么能说出来呢？
- She's on a plane?
- How can you tell that?
因为她不可能游得那么快。
'Cause she can't swim that fast.
听起来不像是一个赎金方案。
Doesn't sound like a ransom scenario.
我猜是血腥的运动，。
饥饿游戏》类情况。
My guess is blood sport,
Hunger Games type situation.
可能是一些以可卡因为燃料的暗网寻宝游戏。。
Possibly some coke-fueled dark web scavenger hunt.
真正的小丑狗屎。我们必须快速行动。。
Real clown shit. We'll have to move fast.
- 我们如何支付给你？
- 加密货币。现金应用程序。
- How do we pay you?
- Cryptocurrency. Cash App.
我将在48小时内把她送回来，否则你的下一次救援是免费的。。
I'll have her back within 48 hours or your next rescue is free.
有多少人需要下一次救援？
How many people need a next rescue?
比你想象的要多。
More than you'd think.
- 我需要那个电话。。
- 我会把它带给你的。
- I'm gonna need that phone.
- I'll bring it to you.
让我知道她在哪里降落。我在那里等你，艾伦。。
Let me know where she lands. I'll meet you there, Alan.
你好。
Hello.
我在哪里？
Where am I?
嗯，你在我的飞机上。
Um, you're on my plane.
这很好，不是吗？嗯？
It's nice, isn't it? Hmm?
座椅是由玛玛拉玛皮革制成的。
The seats are made of mama llama leather.
好了，我要离开你的飞机了。
Well, I'm getting off your plane.
解开我的枷锁!
Unchain me!
那是你的安全带。
That's your seat belt.
你对我进行了麻醉吗？
Did you chloroform me?
人们真的会这样做吗？
People actually do that?
嗯，你知道，它成为经典是有原因的。
Well, you know, it's a classic for a reason.
我的身体感觉喝醉了。
My body feels drunk.
过一会儿就会消退的。我很抱歉。
It'll wear off in a bit. I am sorry.
我只是不能等着你改变主意。
I just couldn't wait around for you to change your mind.
- 不要再玩果冻了。
- 时间不在我们这边。
- Stop playing jelly.
- Time is not on our side.
你看，我们正在挖掘的火山周围的
You see, the volcano we're excavating around
已经患上了严重的消化不良。
has developed a bad case of indigestion.
我比较担心的是，当它爆炸的时候。
I'm rather worried that when it blows,
失落之城剩下的一切都将被摧毁。
everything that's left of the Lost City will be destroyed.
哦，我的上帝。我的腿不听使唤了。
Oh, my God. My legs don't work.
因此，这是我们找到墓穴和王冠的最后机会。
So, this is our last chance to find both the tomb and the crown.
- 哦，上帝。
- 哦!
- Oh, God.
- Oh!
不要担心。这只是我们的最后一次下山。
Don't worry. That's just our final descent.
但这是你生命中最伟大的冒险的开始。
But it is the beginning of the greatest adventure of your life.
欢迎来到失落的城市。
Welcome to the Lost City.
你是怎么找到它的？
How did you find it?
所以，这个城市是建立在熔岩圆顶上的。
So, the city was built on a lava dome.
随着火山的活跃，穹顶充满了熔岩。
As the volcano became active, the dome filled with lava,
和沉没的东西上升到表面。
and sunken things rose to the surface.
D暴露了自己。
The D exposed itself.
- 整个城市？
- 不，不。只是小费。
- The entire city?
- No, no. Just the tip.
我一听到废墟的传闻，就飞过去买下了这个地方。
As soon as I heard rumors of the ruins, I flew over and bought the place.
- 该网站？
- 不，这个岛。南部的一半。
- The site?
- No. The island. The southern half.
我得到了一个很好的交易，因为这里是熔岩流动的地方。
I got a good deal 'cause this is where the lava flows.
我们已经挖掘了一年了。
We've been excavating for a year now.
人们不会在第一天就绑架一个浪漫主义小说家。
One doesn't kidnap a romance novelist on day one.
啊，是的，正如俗话说的那样。
Ah, yes, as the saying goes.
拉菲不喜欢这样。你呢，拉菲？
Rafi doesn't like it. Do you, Rafi?
他说我们不尊重他的遗产。
He says we're disrespecting his heritage.
但在岛上没有很多其他的工作选择，是吗，拉菲？
But not a lot of other job options on the island, are there, Rafi?
乞丐不可能有选择。
Beggars can't be choosers.
我想，没有更多的烤肉了。
No more charcuterie, I take it.
嗯。求你了。我不是一个怪物。
Mmm. Please. I'm not a monster.
无论你需要什么，只要喊一声。
Whatever you need, just shout.
呃，留出一只手。她有一些翻译工作要做。
Uh, leave one hand free. She has some translating to do.
然后呢？
And then what?
洛雷塔，我真的希望你能试试，看看
Loretta, I really wish you would try and see
这对我们来说是一个多么令人兴奋的机会。
what an exciting opportunity this is for us.
我相信这段文字描述了墓穴的确切位置。
I believe this text describes the exact location of the tomb.
这是个逻辑学系统。
It's a logographic system.
像楔形文字或象形文字。
Like cuneiform or hieroglyphics.
现在，如果你有其他文件，可能我可以比较一下......
Now, if you have other documents that possibly I can compare...
是的，那里没有运气。
Yeah, no luck there.
我们在附近的一个瀑布发现了一些抓痕。
We found some scratching at a nearby waterfall,
但这是没有用的。
but it was useless.
只是女人的照片。
Just pictures of women.
听着，我也希望你那亲爱的死去的老考古学家丈夫
Look, I, too, wish your dear old dead archaeologist husband
是来帮忙的，但他不在，所以。
was here to help, but he's not, so,
是时候发光了，洛雷塔，性书作家。
time to shine, Loretta, sex-book writer.
他们会来找我。
They will come for me.
到底是谁呢？
Who, exactly?
你的...你的许多猫？
Your... Your many cats?
哦，我没有养猫。
Oh, I don't have cats.
莫名其妙地更加悲伤。
Somehow even more sad.
我有一只仓鼠，混蛋！
I have a hamster, asshole!
你有一个仓鼠的屁眼？
You have a hamster's asshole?
不，有一个...有一个逗号在...之间。忘了它吧。
No, there was a... there was a comma between... Forget it.
我打赌你哥哥从来没有绑架过任何人!
I bet your brother never had to kidnap anyone!
很高兴见到你，伙计。
Good to see you, man.
- 电话。
- 对。
- Phone.
- Right.
什么？
What?
是的，我在想，我可以，你知道。
Yeah, I was thinking that I could, you know,
也许只是和你一起去。
maybe just sort of come with you.
- 为什么？
- 为了帮助。
- Why?
- To help.
我知道心肺复苏术。我知道一些轻型空手道。CrossFit认证。
I know CPR. I know some light karate. CrossFit certified.
好吧，好吧，听着，听着！
Okay, okay, listen, listen!
我只是...这是我的错。
I just... It's my fault.
而不是绑架之类的事情。
Not the kidnapping and stuff,
但是，我对她说了一些非常刻薄的话，而且我很后悔。
but, like, I said some really mean stuff to her, and I regret it,
而我只需要把它收回来。
and I just need to take it back.
我称她为人类的木乃伊。
I called her a human mummy.
木乃伊是人类。
Mummies are human.
我现在意识到了这一点，是的。
I'm aware of that now, yes.
这倒是真的。
That is true.
请。
Please.
好吧，艾伦，我不能对你负责。
All right, Alan, I can't be responsible for you.
好的，是的。
Okay. Yeah.
- 我需要你呆在车里。
- 是的。
- I need you to stay in the car.
- Yeah.
- 在车上。
- In the car.
- 整个过程中。
- 整个过程中？
- The whole time.
- The whole time?
整个时间。
Whole time.
嗯，嗯。
Mm-hmm.
是的!
Yes!
这就是我。
This is me.
真的吗？海豹突击队就是用这个吗？
Really? Is this what the SEAL teams use?
"只有傻瓜才会以颜色来选择马。"
"Only a fool chooses a horse by its color."
对，对。《道德经》？。
Right, right. The Tao-te Ching?
不，这是在后面租房处的标志上。
No, it was on the sign back there at the rental place.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
什么？什么？
What? What?
我希望能邀请你来吃早餐。
I was hoping to invite you to breakfast,
但看起来你仍有工作要做。
but it looks like you still have work to do.
呃，等一下，等一下，等一下。
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
等待。等待，等待，等待。
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
我相信这是说
I believe this says
"休息 "或 "歇息"。
"rest" or "resting."
因此，它将是。
"卡拉曼和他的宝藏..."
So it would be,
"Kalaman and his treasure..."
然后还有一些缺失的部分，然后 "休息"，"休息"。
And then there are some missing pieces, and then "rest," "resting,"
和一些关于
"眼泪"，所以...
and something about
"tears," so...
在哪里休息？
Resting where?
嗯？哦!
Hmm? Oh!
没说。它没有说。
Didn't say. It doesn't say.
塞奇小姐，我需要你做得更好。
Miss Sage, I need you to do better.
那么下一次也许不要绑架一个浪漫小说家，嗯？
Then next time maybe don't kidnap a romance novelist, hmm?
我的上帝，这不应该是这么难的事！"。
My God, this shouldn't be this hard!
我们要找的不是什么贫民的坟墓。
It is not some pauper's grave we're looking for.
它是一个伟大人物的纪念碑!
It is a monument to a great man!
卡拉曼国王很有野心，他很强大。
King Kalaman was ambitious, he was powerful,
他是第一个在大西洋建造城市的人。
he was the first man to build a city in the Atlantic.
他的臣民的眼睛会转向他。
The eyes of his subjects would have turned to him.
他本来会有一个金字塔，一个紫金塔，一个高塔
He would have had a pyramid, a ziggurat, a tower
来持有他的火之冠。
to hold his Crown of Fire.
我所需要知道的是它在哪里。
All I need to know is where it is.
我不知道你是否记得，但你只说了翻译一下。
I don't know if you recall, but you only said translate it.
我-我翻译了它。
I-I translated it.
再翻译一下。
Translate it again.
有一天，我们会笑着谈论这个问题。
One day, we're gonna laugh about this.
我们正在进行这样的冒险。
Such an adventure we're having.
我应该和你一起去，只是为了做后援，也是为了让你感到可怕。
I should go with you, just for backup and awesomeness.
这是很了不起的。
This is pretty awesome.
你得到了自然，广播。
You got nature, the radio.
是的，你是对的，但它对我非常非常重要。
Yeah, you're right, but it's very, very important to me
她知道我是来救她的。
that she knows that I came to rescue her.
为什么？你喜欢这个女人吗？
Why? Do you like this woman?
不，我只是带了零食之类的东西。
No, I just brought snacks and stuff.
而且她饿的时候会变得有点暴躁。
And she gets a little grumpy when she's hungry.
血压下降。我明白这一点，因为我是一个每天吃五顿饭的人。
Blood pressure drops. And I get that because I'm a five-meal-a-day kind of guy.
顺便问一下，你是酮类吗？你看起来像酮症患者。
Do you keto, by the way? You look like you keto.
- 没有。
- 不，是的。
- No.
- No. Yeah.
你不需要它。
You don't need it.
它是什么？
What is it?
我只是想让她把我当成不仅仅是一个封面模特。
I just want her to think of me as more than a cover model.
但是，艾伦，你是如此之多。你是我的守望者。
But, Alan, you are so much more. You're my lookout.
好吧，我至少可以做我把她放进车里的那部分吗？
Okay, can I at least do the part where I put her in the car
而我只是去。
"嘘，你现在安全了"？
and I just go,
"Shh. You're safe now"?
当然，冠军。她会喜欢这个的。
Sure, champ. She'll love that.
哦，你就这么走了？要开始了？
Oh, you're just going? Going to start?
你现在开始执行任务了？好的。
You're starting the mission now? Okay.
哦!
Oh!
去睡觉吧。
Go to sleep.
- 阿兰。
- 什么？
- Alan.
- What?
这是对信任的破坏，艾伦。
This is a breach of trust, Alan.
我可以帮忙。让我帮忙。
I can help. Let me help.
保持亲密。保持活力。
Stay close. Stay alive.
嘿。
Hey.
去睡觉吧。
Go to sleep.
我得到了他的头。我怎么处理他的头？我只是要把他放下来。
I got his head. What do I do with his head? I'm just gonna set him down.
没有。
No.
嘿，嘿，不！
Hey, hey, no!
不，不，不!
No, no, no!
哦，是的！哦。
Ooh, yeah! Ooh.
嗷嗷叫。
Ow.
团队合作，是的!
Teamwork, yeah!
伟大的努力，艾伦，但那个人已经失去了意识。
Great effort, Alan, but that man was already unconscious.
我已经上紧了发条。
I was already wound up.
只要不在我的时候做...
Just don't do it when I'm...
你好。
Hi.
哦!
Oh!
在你的七号！
On your seven!
哦!
Oh!
训练师，他没有睡着！
Trainer, he's not asleep!
留下来...趴着别动。躺下。
Stay... Stay down. Stay down.
- 你做得很好。
- 谢谢。
- You're doing great.
- Thanks.
你要去哪里？
Where you going?
什么？
What?
洛雷塔-塞奇？
Loretta Sage?
是的。
Yes.
我要带你离开这里。
I'm getting you out of here.
- 你为什么这么英俊？
- 我父亲是一名气象员。
- Why are you so handsome?
- My dad was a weatherman.
A-Alan?
- 是的。
- 你在这里做什么？
- Yeah.
- What are you doing here?
- 呃，不管怎么说，我是来救你的。
- 这并不是...
- Uh, irregardless, I'm here to save you.
- That's not...
- 我想他的意思是 "无论如何"。
- 是的。
- I think he meant "regardless."
- Yes.
哦，呃，她在那里需要拯救吗，训练师？我认为她在那里很好。
Ooh, uh, does she need saving in there, Trainer? I think she's fine there.
不，不，离开它。不要拿他们的东西。他们会来找我们的。
No, no, leave it. Don't take their stuff. They'll come after us.
艾伦，你为什么一直这样做？
Alan, why do you keep doing that?
你为什么一直这样做？我有那个。
Why do you keep doing that? I had that one.
现在只是变得刻薄了。这是不必要的。
It's just getting mean now. It's unnecessary.
我很抱歉。我只是想弄一个进去。
I'm sorry. I just wanted to get one in.
- 请原谅我。能否将我从椅子上移开？
- 没有时间。
- Excuse me. Would it be possible to remove me from the chair?
- No time.
没有时间？已经有这么多闲聊了。
No time? There's been so much chitchat.
我们肯定应该去。
We should definitely go.
我们走吧!我们走吧！
Let's go! Let's go!
为什么事情会发生爆炸？
Why are things exploding?
我得到...
I got...
好的。
Okay.
嘘...
Shh...
嘘。你现在安全了。
Shh. You're safe now.
你是...
You're...
怎么...你怎么会这么冷静？
How... How are you so calm?
- 那是我的...那是我的台词。
- 在这里。
- That was my... That was my line.
- Here.
- 什么？
- 那是灵气吗？
- What?
- Is that Reiki?
- 你在医治我吗？
- 我想是的。
- Are you healing me?
- I think so.
- 啊。
- 正如老子所言："致虚极，以静制动"。
- Ah.
- As Laozi says, "To the mind that is still..."
- "......整个宇宙都臣服了。"
- 嘿，是的，我知道一些...
- "...the whole universe surrenders."
- Hey, yeah, I know some...
我知道一些......嗯......名言，可能对这个时刻有好处。
I know some, um, quotes that could be good for this moment.
In omnia paratus.。
In omnia paratus.
"准备好做任何事。"
"Ready for anything."
也许我们不应该只是深情地凝视着对方的眼睛
Maybe we shouldn't be just staring lovingly into each other's eyes
就像你要坠入爱河，就像我不在这里。
like you're gonna fall in love like I'm not here.
你是谁？
Who are you?
只是一个试图做他的工作的人。
Just a guy trying to do his job.
而现在，这项工作就是要让这位可爱的女士...
And right now, that job is to get this lovely lady...
噢，噢。
Oh! Oh.
哦，上帝。好的。
Oh, God. Okay.
不，发生了什么事？
No. What is happening?
好的。我们该怎么做？
Okay. What do we do?
我们需要做的是...我看不出来。
We need to do... I can't see.
我不喜欢这样!
I don't like it!
在这里。在这里!
Here. Here!
- 你为什么要扔枪？
- 真的吗？
- Why would you throw a gun?
- Seriously?
- 让我从椅子上下来。
- 我不能。我们没有时间了。
- Get me out of the chair.
- I can't. We don't have time.
得挤一挤!你得做个凯格尔运动或什么的!
Gotta squeeze! You got to do a Kegel or something!
- 凯格尔吧!
- 你认为凯格尔是什么？
- Kegel it!
- What do you think a Kegel is?
我不在其中，不在!还是不在！
I'm not in it, not in! Still not in!
- 你得多进去看看。
- 停止。停下来。停止吧！
- You got to go in more.
- Stop. Stop. Stop it!
噢，噢，噢!
Oh, oh, oh!
哦，上帝。快上车，快上车！发动汽车！发动汽车！
Oh, God. Get in the car, get in the car! Start the car! Start the car!
- 走，走。
- 移动你的腿。
- Go, go.
- Move your leg.
- 哪一个？
- 两个人都是！快走！
- Which one?
- Both of them! Move them!
- 前进，前进!
- 好的。好的。
- Forward, forward!
- Okay. Okay.
- 我去！我去！我去我要走了！好的！
- 开车!
- I'm going! I'm going! Okay!
- Drive!
嘘。你现在安全了。嘘。
Shh. You're safe now. Shh.
嗷嗷叫。
Ow.
- 嘘。你现在安全了。
- 不，我不是。不安全。
- Shh. You're safe now.
- No, I'm not. Not safe.
哦，不，我在流血吗？
Oh, no, am I bleeding?
- 我不认为这是你的。
- 哦，不，那是很多的血。
- I don't think that's yours.
- Oh, no, that's a lot of blood.
奶酪和米饭!
Cheese and rice!
- 那些是他的大脑吗？
- 什么？
- Are those his brains?
- What?
我想他的大脑在我的脸上!
I think his brains are on my face!
肯定是他的大脑在我嘴里。我可以品尝到他的思想!
Definitely his brains are in my mouth. I can taste his thoughts!
专注于道路。
Focus on the road.
他只是喜欢训练人。训练者。
He just liked training people. Trainer.
- 你在说什么呢？
- 他爱我。
- What are you talking about?
- He loved me.
你能把车舀到左边去吗？
Can you just scooch the car over to the left?
- 把它拿掉。把它弄下来。
- 哦，上帝。
- Get it off. Get it off.
- Oh, God.
小心点!
Watch out!
噢，噢，噢，噢
Oh! Oh! Oh!
哦，你有没有看到...
Oh, did you see...
没有。
No.
哦。
Oh.
哦，不。哦，不。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
阿兰?
Alan?
哦，神圣的圣诞节。你还好吗？你还好吗？
Oh, holy Christmas. Are you okay? Are you okay?
你认为你能把我从这里弄出去吗？
Do you think you could get me out of here?
是的。好的。
Yeah. Okay.
- 你刚从车里飞了出来。
- 我做到了。我确实做到了。
- You just flew out of the car.
- I did. I did, indeed.
好的，我抓住你了。我得到了你。
Okay. I got you. I got you.
你能把我从椅子上弄下来吗？把我从椅子上弄下来。
Can you get me out of the chair? Get me out of the chair.
你是对的。你是对的。你是对的。
You're right. You're right. You're right.
- 那是...那是锉钉机吗？
- 是的。
- Is that... Is that a nail filer?
- Yeah.
- 你可以直接撕掉它吗？
- 它正在发挥作用。
- Can you just rip it?
- It's working.
也许下一次我会向你扔出一把枪。
And maybe next time I toss a gun at you,
你可以抓住它，而不是躲避。
you can catch it instead of ducking.
下次你向我扔枪的时候，说 "嘿，艾伦，接住 "怎么样？
How about the next time you toss a gun at me, you say, "Hey, Alan, catch"?
那么，也许在你扔掉它之前，先做这个？
Then maybe do that before you throw it?
嗯，"这里 "是 "抓住 "的同义词。
Well, "here" is a synonym for "catch."
不，"这里 "不是 "抓住 "的肉桂。
No, "here" is not a cinnamon for "catch."
以一种口语化的方式，是的，它是。
In a colloquial kind of way, yes, it is.
你说，"给，"我扔给你一件运动衫。
You say, "Here," I toss you a sweatshirt.
你说，"给，"我扔给你一支笔。
You say, "Here," I toss you a pen.
如何'bout只是。
"嘿，接住！枪！"
How 'bout just,
"Hey! Catch! Gun!"
你想扔的任何东西，我都会接住，因为你说过，"接住"。
Anything that you want to throw, I'll catch it because you said, "Catch."
而且我会抓住它，因为你说了。
And I'll catch it because you said it.
这也是一种选择，然后我们会带着枪。
That is also an option, and then we would have a gun with us.
这是个问题。
That's a thing.
- 要小心。
- 好的，我们需要打电话给...
- Be careful.
- Okay, we need to call...
要小心。
Be careful.
我们需要打电话寻求帮助，去机场，然后离开这里。
We need to call for help, get to the airport and get out of here.
- 而我正在开车。
- 好的。
- And I am driving.
- Okay.
哦。哦。哦，哦，哦，哦!
Oh. Oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh!
好吧，叫......叫人帮忙。
Okay, call for... call for help.
你的手机呢？
Where's your phone?
好的。
Okay.
- 告诉我你抓住了他们。
- 我标记了那个金发的。
- Tell me you caught them.
- I tagged the blond one.
哦，洛雷塔。
Oh, Loretta.
你在想什么？
What are you thinking?
你可能已经杀了他们中的一个，但他的伙伴还在她身边。
You might've killed one of them, but his partner's still with her.
而且他显然是熟练的，受过高度训练的
And he is clearly skilled, highly trained
而且非常危险。
and very dangerous.
所以，塞奇小姐说她要离开这个活动。
So, Miss Sage said she was gonna leave the event,
然后上了一辆车，离开了活动现场？
then got in a car and left the event?
- 你试着给她打电话了吗？
- 她没有带手机。
- Did you try calling her?
- She doesn't have her phone.
- 被盗的手机。
- 没有这样说。
- Stolen phone.
- Didn't say that.
我的放大镜在哪里？
Where's my magnifier?
听着，请你帮帮娜娜好吗？
Listen, can you please help with Nana?
我不想让她听到洛雷塔的事情
因为这将使她不安。
I don't want her hearing about Loretta
'cause it's going to upset her.
- 洛雷塔怎么样了？
- 没什么，娜娜。她只是去旅行了。
- What about Loretta?
- Nothing, Nana. She just went on a trip.
- 很好。
- 是的。
- Good.
- Yeah.
那个女孩需要走出家门。
That girl needed to get out of the house.
所以，事情是这样的。Loretta的手机没有被偷。我拿了它。
So, this is the thing. Loretta's phone is not stolen. I took it.
我把它给了艾伦。然后艾伦把它交给了训练师，呃，杰克-训练师。
I gave it to Alan. Alan then gave it to the trainer, uh, Jack Trainer.
而这就是我们发现她的可穿戴性的原因。
And that is how we found her wearable.
- 那么谁是艾伦？
- 潇洒。
- And who's Alan?
- Dash.
- 那是什么？
- 他是她所有书中的英雄。
- What's that?
- He's the hero in all of her books.
- 娜娜。嘿，荡妇。
- 嗯，嗯，嗯。
- Nana. Hey, slut.
- Mm-mmm.
让我们到另一个房间去，谈谈你经历的哪场战争。
Let's go in the other room and talk about whichever war you lived through.
好的。来吧，会很有趣的。我很抱歉。这将是有趣的。
Okay. Come on, it'll be fun. I'm sorry. It'll be fun.
听着，洛雷塔-塞奇失踪了。
Listen, Loretta Sage is missing.
当我看她的智能手表时，它说她已经飞过了
When I looked at her smartwatch, it said that she had flown
到某个我从未听说过的岛屿。
to some island I've never even heard about.
这意味着你们都需要为此做些什么。
That means y'all need to do something about this.
如果你做不到，我会的，这对你来说不是好事。
And if you can't, I will, and that won't look good for you.
很确定这不属于我们的管辖范围。
Pretty sure that's outside our jurisdiction.
- 你必须给联邦调查局打电话。
- 好的。
- You'd have to call the Feds.
- Okay.
如果你真的去找联邦调查局，帮我说说好话。
And if you do go to the Feds, put in a good word for me.
- 对我来说。
- 对我们来说。
- For me.
- For us.
噢，噢。
Oh, oh.
你打算怎么做，把车重新组装起来吗？
What are you gonna do, put the car back together?
嗯...我们可以...
Well... we could...
- 你说电话在哪里？
- 乘客手套。
- Where did you say the phone was?
- Passenger glove.
- 什么？
- 乘客手套箱。
- What?
- Passenger glove compartment.
善哉，善哉。
Goodness.
哦，我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
哦，我的上帝。没有电话，没有车。我们会死在外面...
Oh, my God. No phone, no car. We're so gonna die out...
- 在这里。
- 这是什么？
- Here.
- What is this?
丛林中的靴子。
Boots for the jungle.
这并不完全是登山靴，但...
It's not exactly hiking boots, but...
我想，穿了这么久的高跟鞋，你的脚会很难受。
I figured your feet would be killing you after wearing heels for this long.
这是我们能做的最好的了。它们是艾莉森的。对不起。
It was the best we could do. They're Allison's. Sorry.
哦。好的，好的，谢谢你。
Oh. Okay, well, thank you.
在这里，哦，我给你带来了奶酪。
Here, oh, I got you cheese.
- 哦，我的上帝。
- 你必须保持水分充足。
- Oh, my God.
- You got to stay hydrated.
- 非常感谢你。
- 他们没有玻璃瓶。
- Thank you so much.
- They didn't have glass bottles,
所以我们一定会保留它并回收利用。
so we'll definitely hold onto it and recycle.
好的，所以我们需要做的是找到一个电话，我们需要给当局打电话。
Okay, so what we need to do is find a phone, we need to call the authorities,
而我们需要在这里等待，直到有人来救我们。
and we need to wait here until somebody comes and rescues us.
呃......这......这就是救援。
Uh... This... This is the rescue.
没有其他人会来。
No one else is coming.
- 你说什么？
- 我是救援。
- I'm sorry?
- I'm the rescue.
原本只有我一个人，后来我想，Trainer应该来。
It was originally just gonna be me, then I was like, Trainer should come.
哦，训练师。安息吧。
Oh, Trainer. Rest in peace.
所以，我们最好的办法是去机场。看到这条道路了吗？
So, our best bet is to get to the airport. See this road right here?
从这个区域，只要走一条捷径，穿过丛林就能到达公路。
From this area, just take a shortcut through the jungle to the road.
你刚才说 "穿越丛林的捷径 "吗？
Did you just say "shortcut through the jungle"?
- 是的。
- 好了，你看到我们了吗？
- Yeah.
- Okay, do you see us?
- 嗯，嗯。
- 你不是Dash，我也不是Lovemore。好吗？
- Uh-huh.
- You are not Dash, and I'm not Lovemore. Okay?
我是洛雷塔，你是艾伦。
I'm Loretta, and you are Alan.
- 而丛林会吃掉像我们这样的人，好吗？
- 吃人。
- And jungles eat people like us, okay?
- Eat people.
而且我不想把连衣裙弄脏。它是借来的。所以我们要留在原地。
And I don't want to mess up the jumpsuit. It's on loan. So we're gonna stay put.
我们不会只是站在这里，好吗？
We're not just gonna stand around here, okay?
我们要穿过丛林。
We're gonna go through the jungle,
我们要去机场找一个电话。
we're gonna go to the airport and find a phone,
- 因此，你可以拥有你的蛋糕并得到你想要的东西。
- "也要吃"？
- so you can have your cake and get what you want.
- "And eat it too"?
如果这就是你想做的蛋糕，很好。我们走吧。
If that's what you want to do with your cake, fine. Let's go.
- 这是你对蛋糕做的唯一一件事。
- 不是我的。
- That's the only thing you do with cake.
- Not mine.
我不知道你的人是怎么做的，但我的人吃这个。
I don't know what your people do, but my people eat it.
你可以把它作为礼物送给别人。
You could give it to someone as a gift.
那些人还是要吃蛋糕的。
Those people are still going to eat the cake.
每个人都在吃蛋糕。
Everybody eats cake.
那人们跳出来的那种呢？
What about the kind people jump out of?
- 他们不吃，当他们在里面。
- 哦，我的上帝。
- They don't eat it, when they're in it.
- Oh, my God.
他们绑架你到底是为了什么？
What did they kidnap you for anyhow?
是像Taken那样的一些奇怪的性的东西吗？。
Is it some weird sex stuff like Taken?
哦，我的上帝，谢谢你。
Oh, my God, thank you.
我也这么想，但这家伙是费尔法克斯家族的一员。
I thought so too, but the guy's one of the Fairfaxes.
- 贝弗利？
- 不，是老的那个。
- Beverly?
- No, the older one.
真正奇怪的是，有关于寻找蒙特祖玛宝藏的视频日志。
The really odd one that had the vlog on finding Montezuma's treasure.
那个因试图抬高泰坦尼克号而上新闻的家伙？
The dude that was on the news for trying to raise the Titanic?
是的，他在寻找 "火之冠"。
Yes, he's looking for the Crown of Fire.
等一下。像真正的火之冠？就像那个...
Wait a minute. Like the actual Crown of Fire? Like the one...
- 所以那些废墟是...
- 他们是失落的D城，没错。
- So those ruins were...
- They were the Lost City of D, yes.
- 什么？你现在是在跟我开玩笑吗？
- 嘘。
- What? Are you kidding me right now?
- Shh.
这就像你的书。
This is like your book.
所以我们现在基本上是在进行Lovemore和Dash的冒险？
So we're basically on a Lovemore and Dash adventure right now?
那是什么？
What is that?
如果费尔法克斯真的找到了王冠呢？
What if Fairfax actually finds the crown?
他不会的。他不会的。
He won't. He won't.
- 我们要去哪里？
- 呃...
- Where do we go?
- Uh...
噢，噢，噢。
Oh, oh, oh.
好吧，呃，我们需要下水。
Okay, uh, we need to get in the water.
- 什......什么？
- 我们需要走河道。
- W-What?
- We need to go by river.
不，不，我并不真的做水。
No, no, I don't really do water.
你是什么意思，"做水"？我没有要求你用它来生育。
What do you mean, "do water"? I'm not asking you to procreate with it.
呃，我的身体和水其实并不相配。
Uh, my body and water don't really go together.
你对死亡有什么感觉？哦，上帝。
How do you feel about dying? Oh, God.
嘿，哇，哇，哇。你很好。你没事了。
Hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa. You're okay. You're okay.
- 我得到了你。很好。
- 我会游泳。我会游泳。非常感谢你。
- I got you. Fine.
- I can swim. I can swim. Thank you very much.
- 你要去哪里？
- 我正在穿越。
- Where are you going?
- I'm crossing.
不，我们必须呆在水里。
No, we have to stay in the water.
我为我的书《灌木丛中的一年》研究了水生动物的反跟踪。。
I researched aquatic counter-tracking for my book, A Year in the Bush.
他们会在水中失去我们的踪迹。
They'll lose our tracks in the water.
为什么这里很温暖？等等，你在撒尿吗？
Why is it warm here? Wait, are you peeing?
绕过它就可以了。
Just go around it.
好吧，我想...
Okay, I think...
我想我们失去了他们，对吗？
I think we lost them, right?
是的。这还不算太糟。是的。
Yeah. That wasn't so bad. Yeah.
好的，呃...
Okay, uh...
- 不要惊慌。
- 你是什么意思，不要惊慌？
- Don't panic.
- What do you mean, don't panic?
- 只是不要惊慌。
- 没有。
- Just don't panic.
- No.
不要再说 "恐慌 "了。我现在就很恐慌。
Stop saying "panic." I'm panicking now.
你的背上有东西。
You have something on your back.
不!
No!
- 不要再叫了。
- 那是什么？
- Stop screaming.
- What is that?
- 那是什么？
- 不要再叫了。
- What is that?
- Stop screaming.
- 你身上有吗？
- 不，不。
- Do you have any on you?
- No. No.
为什么你身上没有任何东西？
Why don't you have any on you?
也许那件连体服把他们吓跑了。我不知道。
Maybe the jumpsuit scared them off. I don't know.
- 把他们赶走。
- 哦，我的上帝。
- Get 'em off.
- Oh, my God.
好吧。不，我不能碰那些充血的粘液袋。
Okay. No, I can't touch those blood-gorged mucous sacks.
- 你能甩掉它吗？
- 就在此时。
- Can you fling it?
- Right now.
- 得到它。
- 只要把它捡起来扔出去就可以了。
- Get it.
- Just pick it and fling it.
- 只要把它捡起来扔出去就可以了。
- 你把它捡起来，然后把它扔出去!
- Just pick it and fling it.
- You pick it and fling it!
- 你能把它转出去吗？
- 请把它拿下来。
- Can you spin it off?
- Please, get it off.
我不喜欢碰它。我觉得很晕。
I don't like touching it. I'm feeling faint.
- 他们正在吸走我的灵魂。
- 好了，好了。停，停，停。
- They're sucking my soul out.
- Okay, okay. Stop, stop, stop.
不要发出这种声音。
Don't make that sound.
他们有多少人？
How many of them are there?
哦，没有多少。
Oh, there's not many.
- 感觉有这么多。
- 你是什么...
- It feels like there's so many.
- What are you...
- 我觉得有很多。
- 哦!
- I feel so many.
- Oh!
- 圣母玛利亚!
- 你为什么要祈祷？
- Holy mother of God!
- Why are you praying?
有那么糟糕吗？不可能那么糟糕。有那么糟糕吗？有多少？
Is it that bad? It can't be that bad. Is it that bad? How many?
这不是很好。
It's not great.
他们要把我的每一点都吸出来。
They're gonna suck every bit of me out.
请不要再说了。我只是需要......需要变得低调。
Just please stop speaking. I just need to... need to get low.
稍等一下。
Hold on a second.
哦，上帝！我可以感觉到它们...我能感觉到他们只是......他们只是在吸出这么多。
Oh, God! I can feel them just... they're just sucking out so much.
当他们完成后，我将会像一个干瘪的皮囊。
I'm gonna be like a shriveled-up skin sack when they're done.
你不能告诉我爸爸我是这样死的，好吗？
You cannot tell my dad I died this way, okay?
你得告诉他我在用剑和巨蟒搏斗之类的。
You gotta tell him I was wrestling an anaconda with a sword or something.
我就像一个血色的Jamba Juice。他们只是把它全部吸出来。
I'm like a blood Jamba Juice. They're just sucking it all out.
但为什么它们都在我的屁股上？
Why are they all on my butt though?
有点像从我的凯撒沙拉上摘下鳀鱼。
Kind of like picking anchovies off my Caesar salad.
- 实际上，这并不那么糟糕。
- 鳀鱼？
- It's actually not so bad.
- Anchovies?
你现在为什么要去找食物？
Why do you go to food right now?
只要找到女王，我们就可以结束这一切了。
Just find the queen, and let's be done with this.
我认为你很好。我需要检查一下你的前面。
Think you're good. I need to just check your front.
好吧，我不能看。
Okay. I can't look.
它不好吗？
Is it bad?
- 呃，哇。
- 它是什么？就说出来吧。
- Uh, wow.
- What is it? Just say it.
我的意思是，你期望它，你知道，不...
I mean, you expect it to, you know, not...
然后突然出现了，而且是，呃......。
Then suddenly there it is, and it is, uh...
- 你知道，你为一个人感到兴奋。
- 什么？
- You know, you get excited for a person.
- What?
- 我的意思是，我为所有的人感到兴奋。
- 你为什么会兴奋？
- I mean, I'm excited for all people.
- Why are you excited?
嗯，你知道，人们想知道，他们想知道。
Well, you know, people wonder, they wonder,
但他们不知道，对吗？
but they don't know, right?
他们不知道，直到他们突然知道。
They don't, until suddenly they do know,
然后他们......他们知道一些以前不知道的事情。
and then they... they know something that wasn't known before.
只是...我到底有没有水蛭？
Just... Do I have any leeches or not?
哦，你那勇敢的战士悬挂在宁静的孤独中。
Oh, your plucky warrior hangs in tranquil solitude.
什么？
What?
不，你很好。你很好。
No, you're good. You're good.
我们当时是如此的勇敢。
We were so brave just then.
为什么他们要这么多地去找屁股？
Why do they go for the butt so much?
你唱的那首歌是什么？
What's that song you're singing?
当我还是个孩子时，我的abbi经常给我唱的一首歌。
A song my abbi used to sing to me when I was a kid.
- "如果你从岛上吸食生命...
- 是吗？
- "If you suck life from the island...
- Yeah?
......这个岛会吸走你的。"
...the island will suck of you."
你奶奶给你唱过关于被小岛吸走的歌？
Your grandma sang you songs about getting sucked off by an island?
它并没有翻译得超级好。
It doesn't translate super well.
幻影水蛭综合症，就像，一个东西？
Is phantom leech syndrome, like, a thing?
他们不下蛋，是吗？
They don't lay eggs, do they?
塔哈女王？
Queen Taha?
"卡拉曼国王和他的宝藏得到安息......
"King Kalaman and his treasure laid to rest...
躺在无尽的泪水之井中安息。
laid to rest in the well of endless tears.
躺在无尽的泪水之井中安息。"
Laid to rest in the well of endless tears."
- 那是什么意思？
- 洛雷塔!
- What does that mean?
- Loretta!
你让我心脏病发作。
You gave me a heart attack.
你去哪里了？
Where'd you go?
这是什么？
What is this?
我不确定，但也许他们聚集在这里？
I'm not sure, but maybe they gathered here?
你能想象自己就在这里。
Can you imagine being right here,
当年就在这个地方？
right in this very spot back then?
他们所讲的故事？
The stories that they told?
这么多的历史我相信就发生在这里。
So much history I'm sure happened right here.
他们已经把我们逼到了绝境。
They've got us cornered.
- 好的。我们得上去了。来吧。
- 什么？
- Okay. We've got to go up. Come on.
- What?
你看到我穿什么了吗？我穿着一件闪光的紧身衣。
Have you seen what I'm wearing? I'm in a glitter straitjacket.
无处可去，只能往上走。来吧。我们走吧。
There's nowhere to go but up. Come on. Let's go.
哦！我不应该这样做。我太老了，不适合做这个。
Oh! I should not be doing this. I'm too old for this.
不，你不是。你很美。
No, you're not. You're beautiful.
我没有说我不漂亮。
I didn't say I'm not beautiful.
我说我太老了，不能再这样做了。
I said I'm too old to be doing this.
我的技能是坐着思考，在我无法思考的时候吃东西。
My skill is sitting and thinking and eating when I can't think.
是的，你绝对可以穿更好的鞋子来做这个。
Yeah, you definitely could be wearing better shoes for this.
你给我带来了这双鞋。
You brought me these shoes.
我不能再往前走了。我不能再往前走了。
I can't go any further. I can't go any further.
我在这里做得不是很好。
I'm not doing so great here.
你得到了它。来吧。
You got it. Come on.
我知道你认为你坚持下去会更安全。
I know you think that you're safer holding on,
但你必须继续前进。
but you have to keep going.
- 我不能。我不能，我不能。
- 好吗？
- I can't. I can't, I can't.
- Okay?
- 你闻到了吗？
- 闻到什么？
- Do you smell that?
- Smell what?
- 我闻到了什么。
- 它是一个捕食者吗？它是什么？
- I smell something.
- Is it a predator? What is it?
- 下来的层层叠叠的火？
- 你要闻得更深。
- A downward cascading fire?
- You got to smell deeper.
我什么都没闻到！"。
I don't smell anything!
大口深呼吸。
Take a big, deep breath.
好的。
All right.
- 干得好。
- 好的。
- Good job.
- Okay.
- 那是操纵性的。谢谢你。
- 是的，就是这样。
- That was manipulative. Thank you.
- Yeah, it was.
在这里，我们走了。我来帮你一把，好吗？
Here we go. I'm gonna help you out a little bit, all right?
- 一、二、三...我们来了！
- 你在做什么？
- One, two, three... Here we go!
- What are you doing?
- 离开那里。
- 来吧。
- Get out of there.
- Come on.
- 不，不，不要弯曲。
- 这是我的呼声。
- No, no, don't flex.
- That's my hoo-hoo.
只是骑在头上。保持手的动作，骑在头上。
Just ride the head. Keep the hands moving and ride the head.
- 哦，上帝。
- 你做得很好。
- Oh, God.
- You're doing great.
对不起，我的头发被刮花了。来吧。
Sorry about the scratchy haircut. Come on.
Dulcius ex asperis.。
Dulcius ex asperis.
那是什么？
What was that?
哦，没什么。
Oh, nothing.
这只是约翰和我想说的事情
It was just something that John and I would say
在我们完成了一些大的事情之后，比如说一个...
after we finished something big, like a...
像考古发掘或手稿一样。
like an archaeological dig or a manuscript.
它是拉丁语。它的意思是
"困难之后更甜蜜"。
It's Latin. It means
"sweeter after difficulty."
什么是...
What's...
"洛雷塔是个坏蛋 "的拉丁语是什么意思？
What's Latin for "Loretta's a badass"?
我是个坏蛋。我爬上了一座山。
I am a badass. I climbed a mountain.
哦，我的上帝。我希望贝丝能看到我们这么做。
Oh, my God. I wish Beth could've seen us do this.
- 哦，上帝。贝丝。
- 不要担心贝丝。
- Oh, God. Beth.
- Don't worry about Beth.
她现在可能让整个海军都在追捕我们。
She's probably got the whole navy after us right now.
我明白，你认为你必须自己到岛上的当局去，。
I get that you think you have to go to the island authorities yourself,
但别担心，我将保持洛雷塔的社交活动超级活跃。。
but don't worry, I'm keeping Loretta's socials super active.
刚刚发了推特。
"我刚刚被绑架了吗？"。
Just tweeted,
"Did I just get kidnapped?
#FML，@ShawnMendes。
#ShawnMendes。"。
#FML, @ShawnMendes,
#ShawnMendes."
而你是独自旅行？
And you're traveling alone?
是的，我是独自旅行。嗯，嗯。我是单身。
Yes, I'm traveling alone. Mm-hmm. I'm single.
那么这可能会起作用。
Then this might work.
- 好的!跟我说说。
- 你会打到纽约。
- Okay! Talk to me.
- You'll hit New York.
从那里，你将飞往几内亚，在那里你可以拿起一个水坑的跳板。
From there, you'll fly to Guinea, where you can pick up a puddle jumper.
一个什么？
A what?
- 小飞机。
- 是的，没有腿部空间。。
- Small plane.
- Yeah, no leg room.
这很好。我会接受的。
That's fine. I'll take it.
- 或者你可以直接回家。。
- 谢谢你。
- Or you could just come home.
- Thank you.
我们需要一些更易燃的东西。所有东西都是如此潮湿。
We need something more flammable. Everything is just so wet.
这里有什么？你的包里有什么？
What's in here? What's in your bag?
- 呃...
- 哦，很多。好的。
- Uh...
- Oh, a lot. Okay.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
好的。面罩。
Okay. Face masks.
是的，这就像一个礼品篮的事情。
Yeah, that was like a gift-basket thing.
你带了一根香薰蜡烛到丛林里？
You brought a scented candle into the jungle?
这是我妈妈给我的。
My mom gave me that.
这就像母亲节的一个奇怪的礼物。
It was like a weird gift for Mother's Day.
你妈妈在母亲节送你礼物？
Your mom gives you gifts for Mother's Day?
黑色...
Noir...
桉树迷迭香油。哦。
Eucalyptus rosemary oil. Ooh.
哦，这闻起来不错。
Oh, that smells good.
嗯......哦，好的。好的。
Um... Oh, okay. All right.
Whoo!是的!
Whoo! Yes!
是的，我做了火！我做了火。
Yes, I made fire!
- 那是相当令人印象深刻的。你必须...
- 这是一个美丽的火。
- That's pretty impressive. You have to...
- It is a beautiful fire.
谁会想到呢？
Who would have thought?
哦，你只是，嗯，把你的衬衫脱掉？
Oh, you're just, um, taking your shirt off?
这看起来真的很不舒服。
That looks really uncomfortable.
你还好吗？后面？
Are you okay? The back?
是的。这就是为什么我不做水。
Yeah. That is why I don't do water.
- 好的。
- 我的身体变成了一个八年级学生的脸。
- Okay.
- My body becomes an eighth-grader's face.
你有什么治疗方法吗？比如一些药膏之类的？
Do you have anything for it? Like some ointment or something?
是的，我有。嗯，我有。
Yeah, I do. Well, I did.
它在一个很小很小的瓶子里。
It was in a little, tiny little bottle.
它是这样的。我很抱歉。
It was this. I'm sorry.
哦，上帝，我很抱歉。
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
没关系的。
It's okay.
- 等一下。是的。来这里。到这里来。
- 什么？
- Hold on. Yes. Come here. Come here.
- What?
- 到这里来。坐下来。
- 让我看看。
- Come here. Sit down.
- Let me see.
- 只要坐下来。
- 就在这里？
- Just sit down.
- Right here?
是的。
Yeah.
好的。
Okay.
哦，不，你不必去碰它。没关系的。没事的。
Oh, no, you don't have to touch it. It's okay. It's fine.
我触摸了你们充血的袋子，所以......。
I touched your engorged sacks, so...
- 水蛭。
- 哦，好的。
- The leeches.
- Oh, okay.
好吧，这可能有点冷。
Okay, this might be a little bit cold.
- 对不起。
- 哦，是的。嗯，嗯。
- Sorry.
- Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
对不起，对不起，对不起。
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
也许这就是小飞应该死的方式。
Maybe this is how Dash should die.
可怕的湿疹爆发。真是太性感了。
Horrible eczema outbreak. That's so sexy.
我可以让它发挥作用。
I could make it work.
是吗？
Yeah?
好的，那么。
All right, then.
你会怎么写呢？
How would you write this?
好的。
Okay.
"被芬芳的火焰所温暖..."
"Warmed by the fragrant fire..."
嗯，嗯。
Mm-hmm.
- 开始时很强大。
- 嗯，嗯。
- Starting strong.
- Mm-hmm.
"洛夫莫尔的手探索了......。
"Lovemore's hands explored the...
景观的轮廓
the contoured scenery
小飞的身体。
of Dash's body.
熟悉的地形使
Familiar terrain made
新的和令人兴奋的每一个...
new and exciting with every...
与每一个猩红的边缘"。
with every scarlet rim."
而这并没有，呃...
And that didn't, uh...
没有把她关掉？
didn't turn her off?
没有。
No.
"因为随着每一个心形山脊的出现。
"Because with every cardinal ridge,
洛夫莫尔发现了语言中的另一个字母
Lovemore discovered another letter in the language
只有他们的身体会说话"。
that only their bodies spoke."
他们的身体又在说什么呢？
And what were their bodies saying?
"带我去......
"Take me...
带上我。
take me,
带我去。"
take me."
怎么说呢？
How's that?
这很好。
It was good.
- 你的背部。我是说，你的背怎么样了？
- 很好。
- Your back. I mean, how is your back?
- Good.
- 好的，你确定？
- 是的。
- Okay. You sure?
- Yeah.
- 我也是指我的背。就在那里，是的。
- 好的。
- I also meant my back. Right there, yeah.
- Okay.
用品。
Supplies.
好吧，我感到很冷。我想我可能要进去睡一会儿了。
Okay, I'm chilly. I think I'm gonna probably turn in in a little bit.
- 好的。
- 你还好吗？
- Okay.
- You good?
是的，我是火......很好。我很好。
Yeah, I'm fire... fine. I'm fine.
我不是 "火"。我在火边很好。
I'm not "fire." I'm fine by the fire.
好的。好的。
Okay. All right.
呃，这取决于你，但如果你很冷。
Uh, it's up to you, but if you're cold,
如果你愿意的话，也许我们都能在这里适应。
maybe we could probably both fit in here, if you wanted to.
我们两个人？
Both of us?
- 只有当你想这样做的时候。我的意思是，这只是...
- 是的，不，这听起来...
- Only if you want to. I mean, it's just...
- Yeah, no, that sounds...
呃...
Uh...
好吧，你怎么...
Okay. How do you...
你可以先走，然后我再想办法。
You can go first, then I'll figure it out.
不，不，你去。这绝对是一个
"女士优先 "类型的情况。
No, no, you go. It's definitely a
"ladies first" type of situation.
- 任何时候都不要将手放在袋子里。
- 这就是我打算做的事。
- Keep hands out of the bag at all times.
- That's what I was gonna do.
- 屁股对屁股。
- 手伸出来，屁股对着屁股。
- Butt to butt.
- Hands out and butt to butt.
- 是的。我是做什么的？
- 刚进去。去吧，坐下。
- Yeah. What do I do?
- Just get in. Go ahead and sit.
我先坐？好的，我坐。
I sit first? Okay. I'm in.
你太重了。你会把这东西像游轮一样翻过来。
You're too heavy. You're gonna flip this thing like a cruise ship.
你看着自己。坚持住。我不在。
You watch yourself. Hold on. I'm not in.
为什么这对我的核心有这么大的影响？
Why is this engaging my core so much?
你怎么会有这种想法呢？
How 'bout you shimmy?
- 我不能呼吸了。我不呼吸了。
- 你还好吗？
- I can't breathe. I'm not breathing.
- Are you good?
我的脸。
My face.
是的。好的。
Yeah. Okay.
手伸出来了。屁股对屁股。
Hands are out. Butt to butt.
好的。
Okay.
好吧!
Well!
来吧。
Come on.
来吧!让我们听听吧！
Come on! Let's hear it!
让我们以热烈的掌声欢迎洛雷塔!
Let's give a nice round of applause to Loretta!
这是她应得的。
She earned it.
一个老年闭门不出的人让你们在丛林里握着你们的小弟弟。
A geriatric shut-in left you holding your dicks in the jungle.
干得好，洛雷塔。
Good job, Loretta.
老板，别这样。现在人们正在死亡。
Boss, come on. People are dying now.
你不觉得这一切可能已经走得太远了吗？
Don't you think that maybe this has all gone too far?
这真的值得吗？
Is it really worth it?
我正处于实现无法实现的目标的边缘。
I am on the cusp of attaining the unattainable.
一些单一的东西，一些没有国家的东西。
Something singular, something no nation,
没有一个皇帝，没有一个眉毛胡子一把抓的兄弟曾经有过。
no emperor, no brownnosing brothers ever have.
传说中的火之冠。
The legendary Crown of Fire.
所以，是的。
So, yes.
是的，我肯定会说这是值得的。
Yes, I would definitely say it's worth it.
请原谅我！
Excuse me!
对不起，先生。我需要赶到我的下一个转机航班。
Excuse me, sir. I need to get to my next connecting flight.
没有飞行。
No flight.
飞行员生病了。明天来吧。
The pilot is sick. Come tomorrow.
不，不，先生。我明天不能来。我今天需要做这个。
No, no, sir. I cannot come tomorrow. I need to do this today.
我需要在今晚赶到岛屿Isla Hundida。人命关天。
I need to get to the island Isla Hundida tonight. Lives are at stake.
明天来吧。
Come tomorrow.
- 对不起，小姐？
- 是吗？
- Excuse me, miss?
- Yes?
我忍不住无意中听到你说你喜欢牛排。
I couldn't help but overhear you say that you like steak.
好吧，这有点疯狂。
Okay, this is a little bit crazy,
但我也喜欢牛排。
but I also like steak.
- 什么？
- 我也喜欢牛排。
- What?
- I also like steak.
你是否愿意，也许，我不知道...
Would you like to, maybe, I don't know...
- 也许有一个...
- 不，"生命受到威胁"。
- Maybe there's a...
- No. "Lives are at stake."
我今晚需要到岛上去。
I need to go to the island tonight.
- 啊。
- 是的。
- Ah.
- Yes.
- 甚至更严重。
- 极端的。
- Even more serious.
- Extremely.
好吧，我相信我可能能够帮助你。
Well, I believe that I may be able to assist you.
我有一架货机。
I have a cargo plane.
也许在我送完货后，我们可以去你的岛上转转。
Maybe after I make my delivery, we could swing by your island.
我正要问你一些事情，你最好告诉我真相。
I'm about to ask you something, and you better tell me the truth.
你以前杀过人吗？
Have you ever murdered anyone before?
不!
No!
我不知道我是否真的相信它，但让我告诉你一些事情。
I don't know if I really buy it, but let me tell you something.
如果你想谋杀我，我保证，我会先谋杀你。
If you ever think about murdering me, I promise, I will murder you first.
我的荣幸。
My pleasure.
你很奇怪。我们走吧。
You are weird. Let's go.
"卡拉曼国王和他的财宝在井中安息
"King Kalaman and his treasure laid to rest in the well
无尽的泪水"。
of endless tears."
那是什么？
What is that?
哦，这是一个......这是一个东西。我的意思是，这不是，呃...
Oh, it's a... it's a thing. I mean, it's not, uh...
你知道，这不是你想的那样。
You know, it's not what you think it is.
所以这不是费尔法克斯的古代羊皮纸的碎片？
So it's not Fairfax's fragment of an ancient parchment?
好吧，就是你认为的那样。
Okay. It's what you think it is.
洛雷塔，我以为你比这更聪明。
Loretta, I thought you were smarter than that.
费尔法克斯现在绝不会停止对我们的追捕。
Fairfax is never gonna stop hunting us now.
你在想什么？
What were you thinking?
我们有一座可以埋葬坟墓的火山
We have a volcano that could bury the tomb
在我们到达它之前，在我们看到它之前，在我们保存它的记忆之前。
before we get to it, before we see it, before we preserve its memory.
- 这是...
- 我很抱歉。这就是我们要做的事吗？
- This is...
- I'm sorry. Is that what we're doing?
因为没有人告诉我。你打算什么时候告诉我？
'Cause no one told me. When were you gonna tell me?
我为什么要告诉你？
Why would I tell you?
我们是一起的。我来这里是为了救你。
We're in this together. I came here to rescue you.
你知道你不是Dash，对吗？
You know you're not Dash, right?
你不能骑着白马去救人。
You don't ride in on a white horse to rescue people.
你......给自己喷上古铜色剂，然后站在风力机前。
You... spray yourself with bronzer and you stand in front of wind machines,
这对你来说是很好的。
which is great for you.
你怎么会知道我到底是什么样的人？
How would you have any idea what I'm actually like?
我了解你。你是一本相当开放的书，艾伦。
I know you. You're a pretty open book, Alan.
- 好吧，那我是谁？
- 真的吗？
- Okay, then who am I?
- Really?
是的。
Yeah.
O...好的，呃...
O... Okay, uh...
你是返校节的国王，你靠着你的帅气来到洛杉矶。
You were a homecoming king and you coasted on your good looks to LA,
但后来意识到，作为荒郊野外最英俊的孩子
but then realized that being the most handsome kid in the middle of nowhere
并不意味着你会成为一个明星。
doesn't mean you're going to be a star.
直到有一天，当一个无法出版她的书的女人
Until one day, when a woman who couldn't publish her book
关于西班牙在大西洋的殖民化问题的报告决定写一本浪漫小说。
on Spanish colonization in the Atlantic decided to write a romance novel,
呃，随机选择你作为封面人物。
uh, chose you at random to be on the cover.
你和她很幸运，这些小说取得了巨大的成功。
Lucky for you and her, the novels were a smashing success.
她继续写她的废话，你继续摆姿势。
She kept writing her schlock, you kept posing,
嗯，你知道，我们都没有成为我们希望的人。
um, you know, neither one of us becoming who we'd hoped we would be.
呃，然后有一天，我们都死在了丛林里
Uh, and then one day, we both die in the jungle
在我多年前写的那些大西洋岛屿中的一个。
on one of those Atlantic islands I wrote about all those years ago.
对吗？
Right?
嗯，嗯。
Mm-hmm.
顺便说一句，那是萨拉索塔。
It was Sarasota, by the way.
它不是无处可去。
It's not nowhere.
我在那里与我的母亲和两个姐妹一起长大。
I grew up there with my mom and two sisters.
而且，是的...
And yeah...
我开始做模特
因为我想离开。
I started modeling
'cause I wanted to get away.
这是我唯一能想到的工作。
It was the only job that I could think of
可以带我去所有我一直梦想去的地方。
that could take me to all of the places that I always dreamed of going.
然后终于到了洛杉矶。
Then finally to Los Angeles,
在那里我在你的浪漫小说的封面上摆了一个姿势。
where I posed on the cover of your romance novel.
我非常尴尬，因为我的一个朋友可能已经看到了我。
And I was so embarrassed that one of my friends might've seen me
在你书的封面上戴着假发的人
in that wig on the cover of your book
以至于我好几个月都避免与他们交谈。
that I avoided talking to them for months.
然后有一天。
And then one day,
我正走在回家的路上。
I'm walking home,
我听到这位女士大叫。
"小飞！"
and I hear this lady yell,
"Dash!"
她跑了过来，她是如此的高兴。
She runs up, and she is so happy.
然后我想。
"我怎么会这么难堪
Then I thought,
"How could I be this embarrassed
关于让人如此高兴的事情？"
about something that makes people this happy?"
洛雷塔，你可以做你想做的事。
Loretta, you can do whatever you want.
如果你不想再写，就不要写。
If you don't want to write anymore, don't write.
但是，不要把喜欢你的作品的人说成是白痴，从而减少他们的利益。
But don't minimize the people that love your work by calling it schlock.
这对他们来说是不公平的。
That's not fair to them.
你知道什么是讽刺吗？我以为你是最了解的人
You know what's ironic? I thought you of all people would know
不以貌取人
not to judge a book by its cover.
以封面模式判断一本书。
Judge a book by its cover model.
阿兰?
Alan?
阿兰。
Alan.
他们有两个人。
There's two of them.
- 洛雷塔！我在这里！
- 艾伦!
- Loretta! I'm over here!
- Alan!
艾伦！摩托车和枪，摩托车和枪！
Alan! Motorcycles and guns, motorcycles and guns!
来吧，这边走！
Come on, this way!
停止射击！
Stop shooting!
- 把羊皮纸给他们吧！
- 我不能。
- Just give 'em the parchment!
- I can't.
是的，你可以，实际上。你只要说，"在这里，"然后把它扔给他们。
Yes, you can, actually. You just say, "Here," and throw it at 'em.
对。然后我相信他们会高兴地让我们走。
Right. And then I'm sure they'll happily let us go.
- 好了，继续往下看。
- 他们怎么会一直找到我们？
- Okay, keep down.
- How do they keep finding us?
- 你基本上是一个行走的迪斯科球。
- 我们需要想出一个计划。
- You're basically a walking disco ball.
- We need to come up with a plan.
我有一个想法。
I have an idea.
我们要挖一个洞，扔掉我们的声音。
We're gonna dig a hole, throw our voices.
"我们在这里。"你的声音能像鸟一样吗？
"We're over here." Can you sound like a bird?
- 不，我有一个计划。
- 艾伦，拜托，我在想。
- No, I have a plan.
- Alan, please, I'm thinking.
- 我知道，但我有一个计划。
- 拜托，让我想想...
- I know, but I have a plan.
- Please, just let me think about...
- 等一下。他们在向你射击。
- 是的，这就是为什么我们要躲起来。
- Wait a minute. They're shooting at you.
- Yeah, that's why we're hiding.
不，不，不，不。他们只向你开枪。
No. No, no, no. They're shooting only at you.
他们不会向我开枪。我的大脑才是有价值的。
They won't shoot me. It's my brain that's valuable.
我认为你有时并没有真正听到你说的那些话。
What? I don't think you actually hear the things you say sometimes.
- 也许我可以为你提供保护。
- 你不是在保护我。
- Maybe I can shield you.
- You are not shielding me.
- 我应该保护你。
- 为什么？因为我是个女人？
- I should be shielding you.
- Why? Because I'm a woman?
- 这是极度的性别歧视。
- 好吧，听着，我不认为利用妇女作为人肉盾牌
- That's supremely sexist.
- Well, look, I don't think using women as human shields
正是格洛丽亚-宋飞心目中的改变，你呢？
is exactly the change that Gloria Seinfeld had in mind, do you?
- 格洛丽亚-斯坦尼姆？
- 管他呢。她也是。你知道吗？好吧。
- Gloria Steinem?
- Whatever. Her too. You know what? Fine.
- 请你现在就向我解释一下性别歧视。
- 哦，我的上帝。我是一个女人。
- Please mansplain sexism to me right now.
- Oh, my God. I am a woman.
我无法解释任何事情。
I can't mansplain anything.
呃，我是个女权主义者，我认为女人可以做任何男人能做的事。
Uh, I'm a feminist, and I think a woman can do anything a man can do.
- 我们只需要呆在这里，直到他们累了。
- 我有一个想法。
- We just need to stay here until they get tired.
- I have an idea.
- 我可以告诉你我的计划吗？
- 艾伦!
- Please can I tell you my plan?
- Alan!
这不是一个你可以通过撕开你的衬衫来摆脱的情况。
This is not a situation you can get out of by ripping your shirt off.
不是我的衬衫。
Not my shirt.
三！
Three!
- 是的!
- 哦!
- Yes!
- Oh!
哦。
Oh.
这与我头脑中的想法不同。
That was different than I had in my head.
- 我只是希望我们能阻止他们。
- 会不会是风让它这么做的？
- I just wanted us to stop them.
- Could it have been the wind that made it do that?
不，我认为是我们。我认为......我们做到了。
No, I think it was us. I think... we did it.
我们做过一个人，对吗？但那是，就像...
We did the one guy, right? But that was, like...
我们只是想让他停下来。但我认为另一个人本来可以移动，真的。
We just wanted him to stop. But I think the other guy could've moved, really.
所以，那是......那是在他身上。
So, that was... that one was on him.
即使我们不在这里，这也可能发生。
Even if we weren't here, that could've happened.
你为什么要停在悬崖边上？
Why are you gonna stop next to a cliff?
他们戴着头盔，所以也许他们是...
They were wearing helmets, so maybe they're...
但他们身体的其他部位没有头盔。
But the rest of their body didn't have a helmet.
所以就只有一个头了。
So there'd just be a head.
他们是在鲁莽驾驶，对吗？
They were driving recklessly, right?
在自行车上不要吝啬。
Don't be mean on a bike.
不要在自行车上做卑鄙的事情。
Don't do mean stuff on a bike.
我的意思是，也许他们很好。
I mean, perhaps they're fine.
是的，可能没有。但这也没关系。
Yeah, probably not. But that's okay.
这没关系。你知道，事情发生了。我们走吧。
That's all right. You know, things happen. Let's go.
- 你要把它装回去吗？
- 它是借来的。
- You gonna put it back together?
- It's on loan.
- 看着我。
- 好的。
- Look at me.
- Okay.
我还能做什么，你知道吗？
What more can I do, you know?
你已经做了这么多，贝丝。
You've done so much already, Beth.
我可怜的、可爱的、小娜娜已经失去了视力。
My poor, sweet, little Nana has lost her sight.
这本书的发布是一场彻底的灾难。
The book release is a complete disaster,
其中我已经利用了一切。
which I've leveraged everything on,
所以我现在可能，最肯定是破产了。
so I'm probably, most definitely broke right now.
而最重要的是，我失去了一位作家。
And most importantly, I've lost a writer.
谁会这样做？谁失去了一个作家？
Who does that? Who loses a writer?
好吧，贝丝，你让我想起了我最好的朋友，兰迪。
Okay, Beth, you remind me of my best friend, Randy.
总是为他人着想。
Always looking out for other people,
从不照顾自己。
never taking care of herself.
对不对，兰迪？
Isn't that right, Randy?
她就像我的治疗师，这个人在这里。
She's like my therapist, this one over here.
LOL。"笑出声来"。
LOL. "Laughing Out Loud."
在你照顾好你的朋友之后。
After you take care of your friend,
我们去海滩怎么样？
how about we go to a beach?
- 什么？
- 听着，我在夏威夷有一个接应。
- What?
- Look, I have a pickup in Hawaii.
她不一定要来。
She doesn't have to come.
好的！好的，你可以来！
Okay! Okay, you can come!
她很搞笑。
She's hilarious.
让我问你一件事。
Let me ask you something.
我们都坐在这里闲聊，但谁在驾驶飞机？
We're all sitting here chitchatting, but who's flying the plane?
- 自动驾驶。
- 什么？
- Autopilot.
- What?
先生，到驾驶舱去，驾驶飞机。
Sir, go to the cockpit, fly the plane.
好的。
Okay.
我要去降落飞机了。
I'm going to go land the plane.
好的。
Okay.
不，不，不。带上山羊。求你了，把山羊带走吧。
No, no, no. Take the goat. Please, take the goat.
她在休息。享受飞行
She's on break. Enjoy the flight!
- 你好。
- Hola.
- Hi.
这个英国人走进来，基本上绑架了她。
This English dude came in and basically kidnapped her.
<嗨，我是贝丝。请留言，我马上给你答复。
Hey, it's Beth. Please leave a message, and I'll get right back to you.
呃，你好，贝丝。
Uh, hi, Beth.
是我。
It's me.
呃，我还活着！
Uh, I'm alive!
嗯，听着，嗯...
Uh, listen, um...
呃...
Uh...
我很抱歉，我搞砸了新书巡展。
I'm sorry that I blew up the book tour.
嗯...
Um...
我只是害怕
I was just afraid
和自私。呃...
and selfish. Uh...
哦，艾伦来了。我再打给你。
Oh, here comes Alan. I'll call you back.
所以，呃，警方正在寻找费尔法克斯。
So, uh, police are searching for Fairfax,
而且他们会在我们在这里的时候为我们提供保护。
and they're gonna provide us protection while we're here.
他们有没有说我们会在这里呆多久？
Did they say how long we'd be here?
他们将在今晚晚些时候尝试让我们乘坐水坑跳车。
They're gonna try to get us on a puddle jumper later this evening.
但是，呃，他们说在这期间，旅馆真的很好。
But, uh, they said in the meantime, the inn is really nice,
我们可以洗漱一下，也许还能换件衣服。
and we can get cleaned up and maybe a change of clothes.
好的。
Okay.
好的，是的。
Okay. Yeah.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
来吧。
Come on.
与你的丈夫跳舞。
Dance with your husband.
- 不，不，不。
- 他不是我的丈夫。
- No, no, no.
- He's not my husband.
- 没关系的。
- 与他共舞。
- It's okay.
- Dance with him.
不，不。她不想这样做。她没有合适的鞋子。
No, no. She doesn't want to. She doesn't have the right shoes.
事实上，这是这双鞋唯一适合的地方。
Actually, it's the only thing these shoes are right for.
你不需要这样做。
You don't have to do this.
没事的。没事的。
It's okay. It's okay.
是吗？
Yeah?
我想知道她在说什么。
I wonder what she's saying.
这是民间传说。
It's folklore.
关于一个女人的情歌
Love song about a woman
她的爱人死了，而她不想离开他的身边。
whose lover died, and she didn't want to leave his side.
于是她躺下，拒绝起床。
So she laid down and refused to get up.
一定很吓人。
Must be scary.
不得不面对你的未来，没有和你一起计划的人。
Having to face your future without the person that you planned it with.
那是什么？
What was that?
请原谅我。请原谅我。那个，嗯... 你唱的最后一句话。
Excuse me. Excuse me. The, um... the last line that you sang.
Quién llorará junto a mí?。
¿Quién llorará junto a mí?
"岛屿将在无尽的眼泪之井中为我哭泣。"
"The island will weep for me in the well of endless tears."
那是什么？"无尽的眼泪之井"？那是一个真实的地方，还是...
What is that, the well of endless tears? Is that a real place, or...
天坑的地方。
Sinkhole place.
谢谢你。谢谢你，谢谢你。。
Thank you. Gracias, gracias.
- 来到这里，来到这里。
- 它是什么？
- Come here, come here.
- What is it?
嘿，在羊皮纸上，它说。
Hey, on the parchment, it said,
"卡拉曼国王和他的财宝在无尽的眼泪之井中安息。"
"King Kalaman and his treasure laid to rest in the well of endless tears."
我想也许这是个比喻。
I thought maybe it was a metaphor.
不是的。
It's not.
无尽之泪的井是一个地方。
The Well of Endless Tears is a place.
这是个天坑。
It's a sinkhole.
地图上有一个天坑。
There's a sinkhole on the map.
我认为坟墓就在那里。
I think the tomb is there.
- 这比你的书好多了。
- 什么？
- This is so much better than your books.
- What?
有像...不，我没有任何冒犯的意思。
There's like... No, I don't mean any offense.
- 我是在开玩笑。我是在开玩笑。
- 这就像，平等。
- I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
- It's, like, equal.
- 我是在开玩笑。我是在开玩笑。
- 看看你。你想去那里。
- I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
- Look at you. You want to go there.
- 什么？没有。
- 我可以看到。是的，你看到了。
- What? No.
- I can see. Yes, you do.
那就太疯狂了。这将是疯狂的。我只是...我只是...我只是...
That would be insane. That would be insane. I just... I just...
只是，我们离它如此之近，但是，你知道，我们不能...
It's just that we're so close to it, but, you know, we can't...
没有。
No.
这是你的故事。你想怎么写？
This is your story. How do you want to write it?
我想知道，它就在那里。
I'd like to know that it's there,
这一切都意味着什么。
that all this meant something.
好的。那我们走吧。
Okay. Then let's go.
我们会多呆一天。只要太阳一出来。
We'll stay one more day. As soon as the sun's up,
我们要去找无尽之泪的井。
we're gonna go find the Well of Endless Tears.
- 但如果什么都不是呢？
- 那又怎样？然后我们说我们努力了。
- But what if it's nothing?
- So what? Then we say we tried.
费尔法克斯呢？
And Fairfax?
警察在追捕费尔法克斯。不要为他担心。
The cops are after Fairfax. Don't worry about him.
这很疯狂。
This is crazy.
- 是的，但看看你。
- 什么？
- Yeah, but look at you.
- What?
这是我第一次看到你完全不畏惧。
It's the very first time I've ever seen you totally unafraid.
而且还活着。
And alive.
我去告诉他们我们的计划有变，然后给我们找一辆车。
I'm gonna go tell them our plans have changed and find us a ride.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
我看到你在这里遇到了我的朋友。
I see you met my friend here.
他告诉我你正准备跳上飞机。
He told me you were just about to jump on a plane,
不说再见就走了。
without so much as saying goodbye.
我说，"不可能。不是我的洛雷塔。
I said, "No way. Not my Loretta.
当她是唯一能带我到坟墓的人时，就不会。"
Not when she's the only one who can lead me to the tomb."
不要再这么用力挤压了。
Stop squeezing so hard.
嗷。把你的手从我身上拿开!
Ow. Get your hands off of me!
嗷！放手吧！
Ow! Let go!
我需要一辆车。
I-I need a car.
一辆汽车，一辆汽车。有人有汽车吗？
A car, an auto. Does anybody have an auto?
不，不。不，不。
No, no. No.
我-我-我需要一辆汽车。
I-I-I need an auto.
我可以用我的手表和你交换。
I'll trade you my watch.
这是一块非常昂贵的手表。你有车吗？
It's a really expensive watch. Do you have a car?
这是个宝格丽。这东西在黑暗中发亮。
It's a Bulgari. This thing glows in the dark.
- 它是防水的。
- 我有摩托车。
- It's waterproof.
- I have motorcycle.
很酷，不是吗？
Cool, isn't it?
我总是想，为什么你的个人坦克不能也有一个迷你吧？
I always thought, why can't your personal tank also have a minibar?
喝一杯吧。
Have a drink.
你介意吗？
Do you mind?
呃，是的。
Uh, yes.
恐怕他对你有点怨恨。
He has a bit of a grudge against you, I'm afraid.
关于他的朋友发生的一场摩托车事故？
Something about a motorbike accident his friends had?
你为什么要这样做？
Why are you doing this?
我想要别人没有的东西。
I want something nobody else has.
当我的父亲赠与...
When my father gifted...
正如我所说的。
As I was saying,
当我的父亲把他的帝国赠予
when my father gifted his empire
给我的小弟弟...
to my baby brother...
那是谁？
Who is that?
那是一个骑着轻便摩托车的肯娃娃吗？
Is that a Ken doll on a moped?
我在某个地方认识他。
I know him from somewhere.
哦，我-我-我怀疑。
Oh, I-I-I doubt that.
因为你正在看的是
Because what you are looking at
是一名训练有素的战斗专家。
is a highly trained combat specialist,
在阿富汗、伊拉克的熔炉中锻造。
forged in the furnaces of Afghanistan, Iraq,
科威特, 萨...萨拉索塔...
Kuwait, Sa... Sarasota...
令人难以置信的皮肤。没有湿疹问题。
Incredible skin. No eczema problems.
在我安全之前，他是不会停止的。
And he will not stop until I am safe!
所以你把这个太空舱拉过来。
So you pull this space tank over,
除非你愿意像他的朋友那样灭亡。
unless you would like to perish like his friends did.
他要对他们的灭亡负责。
And he is responsible for their perishment.
他可能不是故意的。
He might not have meant to,
但他们......灭亡了，所以......。
but they... perished, so...
好吧，这是谁--谁？
Okay, who-who is this?
我以前在哪里见过他。
I have seen him somewhere before.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
这是你的封面模特，对吗？
That's your cover model, isn't it?
是的，我知道我在哪里认识他。
Yes. I knew I knew him from somewhere.
上去吧。
Get up there.
并创造性地杀死他。
And kill him creatively.
我喜欢看男人们的失败。
I love watching hunks fail.
我想我要喝那杯酒。
I guess I-I will have that drink.
哦，该死。
Oh, shit.
如果我只是把它顶掉，可以吗？
Is it okay if I just top 'er off?
是的，这很好，但是...
Yeah, that's fine, but...
哦，我的上帝，你以前用过玻璃吗？
Oh, my God, have you used a glass before?
对不起。
Sorry.
Jack Trainer会怎么做？
What would Jack Trainer do?
这里很热。
It's hot in here.
有没有人觉得天气很热？
Anyone else feeling how hot it is?
你是想表现得性感吗？
Are you trying to be sexy?
这非常奇怪。请停下来。
This is very weird. Please, stop.
我可以让你的世界着火。
I could set your world on fire.
睡觉去吧！睡觉去吧！
Go to sleep! Go to sleep!
睡觉吧!睡觉！
Go to sleep! Sleep!
哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
暂停时间。
Time-out.
时间到了!
Time-in!
不！不要向她开枪！我需要她！
No! Don't shoot her! I need her!
哦，天哪!
Oh, Jesus!
嗷，嗷，嗷。
Ow, ow, ow.
移动你的脚!移动你的脚！
Move your foot! Move your foot!
去睡觉吧，混蛋。
Go to sleep, asshole.
到外面去!看!
Get out there! Look!
一个更大的家伙？
A bigger guy?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
什么？
What?
快走吧!
Move it!
不，不，不。不，不，不，不。
No, no, no. No, no, no.
嘿，快进来。
Hey! Get in.
是他还是我？
Him or me?
这不是你那些廉价的、虚无缥缈的女士幻想书，洛雷塔。
This is not one of your cheap, vapid lady-fantasy books, Loretta.
这就是现实生活。
This is real life.
而且我们会杀了他。
And we will kill him.
告诉我们坟墓在哪里。
Tell us where the tomb is.
嗨，那么，不管是谁在负责。
Hi. So, whoever's in charge,
我需要你派官员到这里来。
I need you to send officials to go here.
在这里。
Here.
我们已经关门了。
We are closed.
你关门了？
You're closed?
你知道我一年半来一直想打盹吗？
You know I've been trying to take a nap for a year and a half?
一年半的时间。
A year and a half.
我一直在两头烧蜡烛。
I have been burning the candle at both ends,
凌晨的油。
the midnight oil,
在我的朋友被绑架之前，我就已经开始了。
since way before my friend got kidnapped.
而我想做的是
And all I want to do
是把我的脚踢回来
is kick my feet back
并喝一些酒
and drink some wine
我可能太累了，不能喝酒。
that I'm probably too tired to drink.
而且我想要按摩。
And I want a massage.
我希望有人为我按摩肩膀和脚。
I want someone to massage my shoulders and my feet,
而我同时也想要它。
and I want it at the same time.
如果从逻辑上讲这没有意义，我也不在意。
And I don't care if logistically that doesn't make sense.
因为我一直在努力工作。
Because I have worked hard.
我知道你也有同样的方式。
The same way that I know that you have.
所以我不想问你
So I hate to ask you
让这个地方再开放几分钟。
to leave this place open a few more minutes,
因为如果我们不这样做，
because if we don't,
我的一个非常亲密的朋友和她的封面模特
a very close friend of mine and her cover model
将会死亡。
are going to die.
没有好的办法，老板！
No good way in, boss!
山洞呢？
What about the caves?
那太危险了!
That's too dangerous!
好吧，那我们会非常小心。
Well, we'll be very careful then.
嗯，来吧！
Well, come on!
- 这种方式。
- 我有一个规则，关于
- This way.
- I have a rule about
不进入超级令人毛骨悚然的山洞。
not going into super creepy caves.
- 朱利安?
- 他的名字是朱利安？
- Julian?
- His name is Julian?
他似乎更像巴克或布鲁斯。
He seems more like a Buck or a Bruce.
引领方向。
Lead the way.
去吧。不要害怕。
Go on. Don't be scared.
注意你的脚步。
Watch your step there.
布鲁斯!
Bruce!
- 朱利安。哦，不!
- 朱利安!
- Julian. Oh, no!
- Julian!
哇哦。
Whoa.
嗯...
Well...
让我们不要让他的死亡白费。
Let's not have his death be in vain.
- 向上，向上。
- 你的意思是继续前进？
- Onward and upward.
- What do you mean onward?
我们现在不打算去抓他，是吗？
We're not gonna go and get him now, are we?
哦，伙计。
Oh, man.
- 这没什么。
- 好的。
- It's nothing.
- Okay.
是的。听着，我们还是回到船上去吧。
Yeah. Look, let's just go back to the boat.
这一切都结束了。没有其他人必须死。
This is over. Nobody else has to die.
不，不，不。哈-哈!这是一种微风。
No, no, no. Ha-ha! It's a breeze.
这里有一条隧道。这可能通向坟墓。
There's a tunnel. This could lead to the tomb.
- 这不是人的尺寸。
- 啊，为自己说话。
- That's not person-sized.
- Ah, speak for yourself.
来吧。这几乎是一个儿童滑梯。
Come on. It's practically a kiddie slide.
- 更像是一个岩石括约肌。
- 或者是巨魔的肛门。
- More like a rock sphincter.
- Or a troll anus.
好吧，好吧，你是通过肛门...
All right, well, you are going through the anus...
洞......隧道！
the hole... the tunnel!
- 为什么是她？
- 你是我们煤矿里的金丝雀。
- Why her?
- You are our canary in the coal mine.
不，那是不可能的。我不能。
No, that's impossible. I can't.
如果你通过了，请让我们知道。
Please let us know if you get through.
如果我们没有你的消息，法比奥就得死。
If we don't hear from you, Fabio's got to die.
等等，我是遇难的少女？
Wait, I'm the damsel in distress?
没关系的。我很好。
It's okay. I'm fine.
我做不到。我很抱歉。我不能。
I can't. I'm so sorry. I can't.
- 嘿。
- 什么？
- Hey.
- What?
嘿，你闻到了吗？
Hey, you smell that?
你是说价值几个世纪的蝙蝠粪便？是的，我绝对闻到了。
You mean centuries worth of bat feces? Yes, I definitely smell that.
你得为我大口呼吸。
You gotta take a big breath for me.
你去吧。
There you go.
你可以做到的，洛雷塔。
You can do it, Loretta.
我想我看到了一条出路。
I think I see a way out.
哦，奶酪和米饭
Oh, cheese and rice!
我成功了!
I made it!
看到了吗？完全是安全的。
See? Totally safe.
继续。轮到你了。
Go on. Your turn.
我过来了！马上来，好吗？
I'm coming through! Be right there, okay?
他们为什么要在这里建这个？
Why would they build this here?
但是怎么可能有人会去崇拜
But how is anyone supposed to worship
或记住你，如果他们甚至不能看到它？
or remember you if they can't even see it?
他们不是。
They aren't.
这并不是卡拉曼的权力纪念碑。
This isn't a monument to Kalaman's power.
这是一个悲伤的女人的藏身之所。
It's a hiding place for a grieving woman.
塔哈来到这里，与她死去的爱人在一起。
Taha came here to be with her fallen lover.
她只是想一个人待着。
She just wanted to be alone.
塔哈不希望我们在这里。
Taha doesn't want us here.
天啊，闭嘴吧，拉菲。
God, shut up, Rafi.
这只是火山的问题。
It's just the volcano.
来吧。
Come on.
我们必须继续前进。
We have to keep going.
好了。我们走吧，肌肉男。
All right. Let's go, Muscles.
把它打开。
Open it up.
- 不要打扰他们。
- 她将佩戴头饰。
- Don't disturb them.
- She will be wearing the headdress.
来吧。我们大老远跑来不是为了表达我们的敬意。
Come on. We didn't come all this way just to pay our respects.
我不能，嗯...
I can't, um...
- 呃...
- 我很抱歉，abuela.。
- Uh...
- I'm sorry, abuela.
那是什么？
What is that?
那些是......贝壳吗？
Are those... seashells?
皇冠是用贝壳做的？
The crown is made of seashells?
宝藏在哪里？
Where's the treasure?
她正抱着他。
She's holding him.
你是说那个死去的人？
You mean the dead guy?
看。
Look.
这是他们的求爱。
It's their courtship.
卡拉曼正在岛上寻找什么。
Kalaman is searching the island for something.
罕见的红贝壳。
Rare red seashells.
为了证明他的爱，他在一年内每天给她一个贝壳。
To prove his love, he gave her one shell every day for a year
并把它们做成了一个皇冠。
and made them into a crown,
鲜红的颜色像他们爱情的火焰。
bright red like the flame of their love,
直到有一天，她接受了他的求婚。
until the day came where she accepted his proposal.
这从来不是关于珠宝的问题。
It was never about jewels.
卡拉曼和塔哈的财富并不是物质的。
Kalaman and Taha's riches weren't material.
那是他们的爱。
It was their love.
这就是它的意义。这就够了。
That's what it meant. That was enough.
就这样了？
So that's it?
所有这些时间和金钱
All of that time and money
花在什么地方，只是一个廉价的比喻？
spent on, what, just a cheap metaphor?
- 这是一个相当丰富的比喻。
- 哦，闭嘴！
- It's a pretty rich metaphor.
- Oh, shut up!
我们得走了。我们现在得走了。
We got to go. We got to go now.
- 来吧。我们走吧。
- 不，不，不。你要留在这里。
- Come on. Let's go.
- No, no, no. You are staying here.
你认为这一切是如此甜蜜和诗意。
You think it's all so sweet and poetic.
好吧，那么你可以留在这里，度过你最后的时光
Well, then you can stay here and spend your last moments
思考这个比喻的丰富性。
pondering the richness of that metaphor.
- 进入。
- 什么？来吧，伙计。
- Get in.
- What? Come on, man.
- 哦，上帝。快进去吧。进到坟墓里去。
- 好的，好的。
- Oh, God. Just get in. Get in the tomb.
- Okay, okay.
我想，被活埋总比被埋死好。
It's better to be buried alive than buried dead, I guess.
- 这真的不是。
- 你知道，这是一个耻辱，真的。
- It's really not.
- You know, it is a shame, really.
这是一个地狱般的故事。
This is a hell of a story.
可惜你不在身边，无法讲述。来吧。
Pity you won't be around to tell it. Come on.
- 但他们会死。
- 你也会
- But they'll die.
- So will you
如果你不停止成为这样一个雪花！到这里来！
if you don't stop being such a snowflake! Get over here!
这很好。这不是一个活跃的恶梦
This is fine. This is not an active nightmare
我从14岁开始就有了。
I've had since I was 14 years old.
嗷!
Ow!
你为什么要走得这么快？这不是一场比赛。
Why are you going so fast? It's not a race.
等等，不！你在做什么？回到这里来！
Wait, no! What are you doing? Come back here!
你可能已经买下了这个岛，但现在这个岛拥有你了！"。
You may have bought the island, but now the island owns you!
你不能把我丢在这里！
You can't just leave me here!
拉菲！回来吧！
Rafi! Come back!
我需要一艘船!
I need a boat!
嘿，嘿，停下来！停下来！
Hey, hey, stop! Stop!
救命啊!救命啊!
Help! Help!
一个当地人刚刚偷了我的船!
One of the locals just stole my boat!
你见过一个女人吗？
Have you seen a woman?
她是一个身穿亮片连衣裙的黑发女子。
She's a brunette in a sequined jumpsuit.
不，她是不是遇到了什么麻烦？
No. Is she in some sort of trouble?
这有点好笑。
It's kind of funny.
我过去一直认为这...
I used to think this...
这种事情是如此浪漫。
this sort of thing was so romantic.
是吗？
Yeah?
被锁在一个即将被熔岩埋葬的棺材里。
Being locked in a coffin about to be buried by lava,
还是......搂着死人？
or... cuddling dead people?
只是和失去的爱情躺在一起。
Just laying down with a lost love.
像塔哈那样。
Like Taha did.
- 上帝。
- 哦...
- God.
- Oh...
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉，我没能救你。
I'm sorry that I couldn't save you.
我很抱歉我不能成为小飞。
I'm sorry I couldn't be Dash.
你是对的。
You're right.
你一点也不像小飞。
You're nothing like Dash.
你并没有骑着白马来救我。
You didn't ride in on a white horse to save me.
你骑着一辆......借来的摩托车，消声器坏了。
You rode in on a... borrowed scooter with a broken muffler.
是的。
Yeah.
我永远不可能写出像你这样的大飞。
I never could've written a Dash like you.
因为我从来不知道
'Cause I never knew
一个像艾伦一样的小飞。
a Dash like Alan.
我是如此害怕再次被生活所伤害
I was so afraid of being hurt by life again
我只是停止了生活。
that I just stopped living.
看不到眼前的美好事物。
Couldn't see the good things in front of me.
我只是很抱歉我没有早点看到你。
I'm just so sorry I didn't see you sooner.
我也有一个忏悔。
I have a confession too.
看，我真的很喜欢我们这个新故事的走向。
See, I was really liking where this new story of ours was headed.
我只是想看看结果会如何，我猜。
I just wanted to see how it was gonna turn out, I guess.
《洛雷塔和艾伦的冒险》。
The Adventures of Loretta and Alan.
不，它需要一个比这更好的标题。
No, it would need a better title than that.
是的，当然。肯定是的。
Yeah, definitely. Definitely.
对不起。只是...塔哈的大腿骨在戳我。
Sorry. Just... Taha's femur is poking me.
拉菲一定留下了这个。
Rafi must have left that.
你怎么会忘记你的撬棍呢？它可以帮助我们逃跑。
How do you forget your crowbar? It's gonna help us escape.
不，他是故意留下的。
No, he left it on purpose.
哦，酷。我一直喜欢他。
Oh, cool. I always liked him.
- 一...
- 好的。
- One...
- Okay.
- ...二，三！
- 好的。
- ...two, three!
- Okay.
我希望他一开始就不要把我们留在这里，但是......。
I would've preferred him to not leave us here in the first place, but...
好的。
Okay.
Dulcius ex asperis.。
Dulcius ex asperis.
困难之后更加甜蜜。
Sweeter after difficulty.
上去吧！往树上跑!
Go up! Run for the trees!
等等。不对。不要紧。树木着火了。
Wait. Nope. Never mind. Trees are on fire.
好的。
Okay.
我们可以通过隧道回去。
We can go back through the tunnel.
没有。隧道是不可能的。
Nope. Tunnel's a no-go.
嗯，好的。我对其他想法持开放态度。
Um, okay. I'm open to other ideas.
这里有一股水流。我们可以沿着它进入海洋。
There's a current. We can follow it into the ocean.
我们怎么知道另一边有什么？
How do we know what's on the other side?
我们不知道。
We don't.
只有一个办法可以找到答案。
There's only one way to find out.
- 值得出疹子。
- 是吗？
- Worth the rash.
- Yeah?
阿兰?
Alan?
艾伦!
Alan!
阿兰?
Alan?
A...阿兰?
A... Alan?
艾伦!
Alan!
哦，我的上帝！你还活着！"。你还活着！
Oh, my God! You're alive!
- 我还活着。
- 哦，我的上帝。我以为我杀了你。
- I'm alive.
- Oh, my God. I thought I killed you.
那是贝丝吗？
Is that Beth?
洛雷塔!
Loretta!
贝丝!
Beth!
- 贝丝!
- Beth!
贝丝!
Beth!
贝丝，你来了！
Beth, you're here!
你为什么在这里？
Why are you here?
我告诉过你，我支持你，女孩!
I told you I got your back, girl!
我很抱歉!
I'm so sorry!
我毁了那件连衣裙！"。
I destroyed the jumpsuit!
什么？
What?
不要紧!以后再说。
Never mind! Later.
我在一个山洞里发现了一个英国人。
I found a British guy in a cave.
我以为他是个小男孩，但他有满脸的胡须。
I thought he was a little boy, but he has a full beard.
贝丝，那是费尔法克斯！他绑架了我们！
Beth, that's Fairfax! He kidnapped us!
他是个坏家伙，贝丝！他杀了我的训练师！
He's a bad guy, Beth! He killed my trainer!
抓住他！
Get him!
阻止他！
Stop him!
我支持你，女孩。
I got your back, girl.
你在哪里跑？那是一条船。
Where were you running? It's a boat.
这家伙太搞笑了。
This guy's hilarious.
找到你了。
Got you.
游到岩石那边去!
Swim over to the rock!
- 我没有得到你。不，我得到了你。
- 我抓住了你。
- I don't got you. No, I got you.
- I got you.
我们会抓住你的。会好起来的。
We're gonna get you. It's gonna be okay.
"在附近的岩石上找到避难所，"。
"Finding refuge on a nearby rock,
他把她从水中抱起，。
he lifted her from the water,
他强有力的手臂将她的身体拉近。
his powerful arms pulling her body close.
阿兰小声说......"。
Alan whispered..."
嘘。你现在安全了。
Shh. You're safe now.
"在那一刻，洛雷塔可以感觉到新的冒险刚刚开始。"。
"In that moment, Loretta could feel a new adventure was just beginning."
"狭路相逢勇者胜"，令人心潮澎湃的激情
"The heart-pounding passion of the narrow escape
这只会激起洛雷塔对他的欲望。
only inflamed Loretta's desire for him.
她渴求着即将从他身上涌出的热熔岩......"。
She was thirsty for the hot lava soon to be pulsing from his..."
你不要在好的部分就停止了。
Don't you go stopping right at the good part.
这没有什么是她以前没有读过的。
It's nothing she hasn't read before.
我没有告诉你吗？
Didn't I tell you?
世界上最美丽的海滩。
The most beautiful beach in the world.
也许以后，我会带你看看迷人的海湾？
Maybe later, I'll show you the Cove of Enchantment?
不，你可以带走兰迪。
No, you can take Randy.
记住，你是我的柏拉图式的男人朋友。
Remember, you are my platonic man friend.
柏拉图式？我喜欢这句话的意思。
Platonic? I like the sound of that.
不知道它是什么意思，但我喜欢它的声音。
Not sure what it means, but I like the sound of it.
给你，兰迪。
Here you go, Randy.
- 我亲爱的。
- 你是一个天使。谢谢你。
- My dear.
- You are an angel. Thank you.
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
- 结束图书之旅的好方法，对吗？
- 嗯，嗯。
- Nice way to end a book tour, right?
- Mm-hmm.
嗯...
Um...
你知道，其实我有一句话，我喜欢在这样的时刻使用。
You know, I have a phrase I like to use in moments like these, actually.
嗯...
Um...
Quid deinde？
Quid deinde?
它是拉丁语。它的意思是，呃，"接下来是什么？"
It's Latin. It means, uh, "What's next?"
Quid cogitas？
Quid cogitas?
嗯。
Mmm.
Buca di Beppo.
- 是的，我对其他拉丁文一无所知。
- 不，是的。
- Yeah. I know zero other Latin.
- No. Yes.
我为现在这个时刻查了一下。
I looked it up for this moment right now.
那么，接下来是什么呢？
So, what does come next?
- 你会怎么写呢？
- 我不知道。
- How would you write this?
- I don't know.
- 你会怎么写呢？
- 我们真的要我写这个吗？
- How would you write it?
- Do we really want me to write this?
- 只是尝试。试一试吧。
- 好吧，我写吧。
- Just try. Take a stab at it.
- Okay. I'll write it.
好的。
Okay.
"我们当时...他们，呃......站在一个海滩上。"
"We were... They were, uh... standing on a beach."
为观众搭建了舞台。他们知道我们在哪里。
Sets the stage for the audience. They know where we are.
你已经在笑了。你为什么要笑我？
You're already laughing. Why are you laughing at me?
- 我不是在笑。我是在笑。
- 你是。
- I'm not laughing. I'm smiling.
- You are.
"在褐色的棕榈树上面有
"There are palm trees above a brown
头发像树皮一样的少女。
bark-like hair of the maiden.
有一个死水母..."
There is a dead jellyfish..."
你所做的只是描述你现在实际看到的东西。
All you're doing is describing what you're actually seeing right now.
"他很紧张，因为他真的喜欢她。"
"He's nervous because he really likes her."
写得不错。
It's nice writing.
- 谢谢。
- 不客气。
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
我将继续下去。
I'll keep going.
"他深深地看了她的眼睛。
"He looked deep in her eyes.
唯一能与那片海洋的脉搏相比的是
The only thing that could compare to the pulse of that ocean
是在......的悸动。"
was the throbbing in the..."
- 好吧，不，你不能悸动。
- 为什么不呢？
- Okay, no, you can't throb.
- Why not?
不能带着悸动出场。
Can't come out of the gate with a throb.
- 你一直在悸动。
- 我没有带着它出场。
- You throb all the time.
- I don't come out of the gate with it.
- 你必须赢得这种悸动。
- 谁让你成为悸动女王的？
- You have to earn the throb.
- Who made you the queen of throb?
这通常是第四章的事情。你想让它在第四章适当地提出来。
It's usually a chapter four thing. You want it brought up appropriately in four.
我想你在所有的章节中都会悸动。
"脉动"。
I think you throb in all the chapters.
"Pulsating."
它是悸动的前奏。
It's a precursor to throb.
- "起伏不定"。
- 你刚刚跳到了五个。
- "Undulating."
- You just jumped to five.
- 他们只是接吻怎么样？为什么不呢？
- 就像一个普通的吻？
- How 'bout they just kiss? Why not?
- Just like a regular kiss?
是的。就像一个章节的开头之吻。
Yeah. Like a beginning-of-the-chapter kiss.
我很善于开始...
I'm good at starting...
情况如何？有笔记吗？
How was that? Any notes?
第一章的尝试非常好。
Very good first chapter attempt.
噗!
Psst!
注意。
Psst.
母亲...
Mother...
你已经死了。
You were dead.
你的脑浆从你的脸上流出来，打在我的喉咙后面。
Your brains came out of your face and hit the back of my throat.
- 他在我的嘴里。
- 不要说他在你的嘴里。
- He was in my mouth.
- Don't say he was in your mouth.
- 我可以品尝到你。
- 千万别这么说。
- I could taste you.
- Don't ever say that.
我们只用了10%的大脑，所以我刚刚换了另外10%。
We only use 10% of our brain, so I just switched to another 10%.
那么，你还好吗？
So, you're okay?
百分之百。
One hundred percent.
意思是10%。
Meaning 10%.
我们以为你已经死了。
We thought you were dead.
自然，我有一些愤怒的问题，我需要放下。
Naturally, I have some anger issues I need to let go of.
- 当然了。
- 还有怨恨。
- Of course.
- And resentment.
见到你真好，伙计。
So good to see you, man.
好了，让我们把话说得更少。
Okay, let's keep the chatter down.
我们正在闭上眼睛，重新与我们的呼吸联系起来。
We're closing our eyes and reconnecting to our breath.
很好。
Great.